<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>The catalogue of most of the memorable tombes, grave-stones, plates, escutcheons, or atchievements in the demolisht or yet extant churches of London from St. Katharines beyond the Tower to Temple-Barre the out parishes being included : a work of great weight and conseqvently to be indulged and contenanced by such who are gratefully ambitious of preserving the memory of their ancestors / by P. Fisher somtimes Serjant Major of Foot.</title>
            <author>Fisher, Payne, 1616-1693.</author>
         </titleStmt>
         <editionStmt>
            <edition>
               <date>1668</date>
            </edition>
         </editionStmt>
         <extent>Approx. 124 KB of XML-encoded text transcribed from 31 1-bit group-IV TIFF page images.</extent>
         <publicationStmt>
            <publisher>Text Creation Partnership,</publisher>
            <pubPlace>Ann Arbor, MI ; Oxford (UK) :</pubPlace>
            <date when="2013-12">2013-12 (EEBO-TCP Phase 2).</date>
            <idno type="DLPS">A39530</idno>
            <idno type="STC">Wing F1014</idno>
            <idno type="STC">ESTC R28628</idno>
            <idno type="EEBO-CITATION">10700854</idno>
            <idno type="OCLC">ocm 10700854</idno>
            <idno type="VID">45532</idno>
            <availability>
               <p>To the extent possible under law, the Text Creation Partnership has waived all copyright and related or neighboring rights to this keyboarded and encoded edition of the work described above, according to the terms of the CC0 1.0 Public Domain Dedication (http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/). This waiver does not extend to any page images or other supplementary files associated with this work, which may be protected by copyright or other license restrictions. Please go to https://www.textcreationpartnership.org/ for more information about the project.</p>
            </availability>
         </publicationStmt>
         <seriesStmt>
            <title>Early English books online.</title>
         </seriesStmt>
         <notesStmt>
            <note>(EEBO-TCP ; phase 2, no. A39530)</note>
            <note>Transcribed from: (Early English Books Online ; image set 45532)</note>
            <note>Images scanned from microfilm: (Early English books, 1641-1700 ; 1402:17)</note>
         </notesStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <biblFull>
               <titleStmt>
                  <title>The catalogue of most of the memorable tombes, grave-stones, plates, escutcheons, or atchievements in the demolisht or yet extant churches of London from St. Katharines beyond the Tower to Temple-Barre the out parishes being included : a work of great weight and conseqvently to be indulged and contenanced by such who are gratefully ambitious of preserving the memory of their ancestors / by P. Fisher somtimes Serjant Major of Foot.</title>
                  <author>Fisher, Payne, 1616-1693.</author>
               </titleStmt>
               <extent>[6], 52 p.   </extent>
               <publicationStmt>
                  <publisher>[s.n.],</publisher>
                  <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
                  <date>1668.</date>
               </publicationStmt>
               <notesStmt>
                  <note>Reproduction of original in the British Library.</note>
               </notesStmt>
            </biblFull>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
      <encodingDesc>
         <projectDesc>
            <p>Created by converting TCP files to TEI P5 using tcp2tei.xsl,
      TEI @ Oxford.
      </p>
         </projectDesc>
         <editorialDecl>
            <p>EEBO-TCP is a partnership between the Universities of Michigan and Oxford and the publisher ProQuest to create accurately transcribed and encoded texts based on the image sets published by ProQuest via their Early English Books Online (EEBO) database (http://eebo.chadwyck.com). The general aim of EEBO-TCP is to encode one copy (usually the first edition) of every monographic English-language title published between 1473 and 1700 available in EEBO.</p>
            <p>EEBO-TCP aimed to produce large quantities of textual data within the usual project restraints of time and funding, and therefore chose to create diplomatic transcriptions (as opposed to critical editions) with light-touch, mainly structural encoding based on the Text Encoding Initiative (http://www.tei-c.org).</p>
            <p>The EEBO-TCP project was divided into two phases. The 25,368 texts created during Phase 1 of the project (2000-2009), initially available only to institutions that contributed to their creation, were released into the public domain on 1 January 2015. The approximately 40,000 texts produced during Phase 2 (2009- ), of which 34,963 had been released as of 2020, originally similarly restricted, were similarly freed from all restrictions on 1 August 2020. As of that date anyone is free to take and use these texts for any purpose (modify them, annotate them, distribute them, etc.). But we do respectfully request that due credit and attribution be given to their original source.</p>
            <p>Users should be aware of the process of creating the TCP texts, and therefore of any assumptions that can be made about the data.</p>
            <p>Text selection was based on the New Cambridge Bibliography of English Literature (NCBEL). If an author (or for an anonymous work, the title) appears in NCBEL, then their works are eligible for inclusion. Selection was intended to range over a wide variety of subject areas, to reflect the true nature of the print record of the period. In general, first editions of a works in English were prioritized, although there are a number of works in other languages, notably Latin and Welsh, included and sometimes a second or later edition of a work was chosen if there was a compelling reason to do so.</p>
            <p>Image sets were sent to external keying companies for transcription and basic encoding. Quality assurance was then carried out by editorial teams in Oxford and Michigan. 5% (or 5 pages, whichever is the greater) of each text was proofread for accuracy and those which did not meet QA standards were returned to the keyers to be redone. After proofreading, the encoding was enhanced and/or corrected and characters marked as illegible were corrected where possible up to a limit of 100 instances per text. Any remaining illegibles were encoded as &lt;gap&gt;s. Understanding these processes should make clear that, while the overall quality of TCP data is very good, some errors will remain and some readable characters will be marked as illegible. Users should bear in mind that in all likelihood such instances will never have been looked at by a TCP editor.</p>
            <p>The texts were encoded and linked to page images in accordance with level 4 of the TEI in Libraries guidelines.</p>
            <p>Copies of the texts have been issued variously as SGML (TCP schema; ASCII text with mnemonic sdata character entities); displayable XML (TCP schema; characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or text strings within braces); or lossless XML (TEI P5, characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or TEI g elements).</p>
            <p>Keying and markup guidelines are available at the <ref target="http://www.textcreationpartnership.org/docs/.">Text Creation Partnership web site</ref>.</p>
         </editorialDecl>
         <listPrefixDef>
            <prefixDef ident="tcp"
                       matchPattern="([0-9\-]+):([0-9IVX]+)"
                       replacementPattern="http://eebo.chadwyck.com/downloadtiff?vid=$1&amp;page=$2"/>
            <prefixDef ident="char"
                       matchPattern="(.+)"
                       replacementPattern="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/textcreationpartnership/Texts/master/tcpchars.xml#$1"/>
         </listPrefixDef>
      </encodingDesc>
      <profileDesc>
         <langUsage>
            <language ident="eng">eng</language>
         </langUsage>
         <textClass>
            <keywords scheme="http://authorities.loc.gov/">
               <term>Sepulchral monuments --  England --  London.</term>
               <term>Great Britain --  Genealogy.</term>
            </keywords>
         </textClass>
      </profileDesc>
      <revisionDesc>
         <change>
            <date>2012-08</date>
            <label>TCP</label>Assigned for keying and markup</change>
         <change>
            <date>2012-08</date>
            <label>Apex CoVantage</label>Keyed and coded from ProQuest page images</change>
         <change>
            <date>2012-10</date>
            <label>Simon Charles</label>Sampled and proofread</change>
         <change>
            <date>2012-10</date>
            <label>Simon Charles</label>Text and markup reviewed and edited</change>
         <change>
            <date>2013-02</date>
            <label>pfs</label>Batch review (QC) and XML conversion</change>
      </revisionDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text xml:lang="eng">
      <front>
         <div type="title_page">
            <pb facs="tcp:45532:1" rendition="simple:additions"/>
            <p>THE CATALOGUE of Moſt of the Memorable Tombes, Grave-ſtones, Plates, Eſcutcheons, or Atchievements in the Demoliſht or yet Extant Churches of LONDON from St <hi>Katharines</hi> beyond the Tower, to <hi>Temple-Barre.</hi> The Out-Pariſhes being included A WORK OF GREAT WEIGHT, AND CONSEQVENTLY to be indulged and Countenanced by ſuch who are gratefully ambitious of Preſerving the Memory of their anceſtors.</p>
            <p>By <hi>P. Fiſher</hi> ſometimes Serjant Major of Foot.</p>
            <p>
               <hi>LONDON</hi> Printed Anno. MDCLXVIII.</p>
         </div>
      </front>
      <body>
         <div type="catalogue">
            <pb facs="tcp:45532:2"/>
            <pb facs="tcp:45532:2"/>
            <head>The Catalogue of the moſt Memorable perſons who had viſible Tombs, plated Grave-ſtones, Eſcutcheons or Hatch<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ments in the City of <hi>London</hi> before the laſt dreadful Fire.</head>
            <list>
               <item>SIR <hi>Philip Sydney</hi> one of the moſt noble anceſtors of the Right honourable Robert Earle of Leiceſter now living.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Francis Walſingham</hi> Knight, principal Secretary of ſtate to Q. <hi>Elizabeth.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Chriſtopher Hatton</hi> Knight, one of the noble anceſtors of the Right honourable the Lord Hatton now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Clifford</hi> Biſhop of Lon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>don, a branch of thoſe Hero<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ique and brave Martial Clif<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fords late Earles of Cumber<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>land.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Michael</hi> de <hi>Northburgh</hi> Biſhop of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Euſtachius</hi> de <hi>Fauconberg</hi> Biſhop of London one of the noble anceſtors of the Right honou<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rable Thomas Lord Bellaſis, viſcount Fauconberg now living</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Laurentius</hi> de <hi>Allerthorp</hi> Trea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſurer.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Worsley</hi> Dean of S. Pauls, a branch of that flouriſh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ing and knightly Family of the Worſleys in the Iſle of Wight, of which Sir Robert Worſley Baronet now living is chief.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Roger Brabazon</hi> Doctor of the Civill Laws.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Baskervile</hi> Knight, Generall of the Engliſh forces in Picardy, of the noble Line and Family of the Baskerviles in the County of Hereford.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henricus</hi> a <hi>Wengham</hi> Lord Chancellour of England.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Erkenwaldus</hi> the 3. Biſhop of London after the coming in of the Saxons.</item>
               <pb facs="tcp:45532:3"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Sebba</hi> King of the laſt Saxons.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Etheldred</hi> King of England.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Poultney</hi> four times Major of London anceſtor to Sir William Poultney Knight now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Hewit</hi> Eſq; one of the anceſtors of the flouriſhing and Knightly Family of the Hewits in Hartfordſhire and elſe where</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John</hi> of <hi>Gaunt</hi> Duke of Lanca<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſter.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robertus Hare</hi> Treaſurer of St. Pauls, one of the anceſtors of the Right honourable Lord Henry Hare Baron of Colrain now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Creek</hi> Doctor of the Civill Law.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Cockain</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior of London one of the worthy anceſtors of the Right honourable of the Lord Cock<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ain viſcount Cullen now living.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Detrick</hi> King at Armes.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Detrick</hi> his Son, Knight, and likewiſe King at Armes.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gulielmus</hi> the Norman, Biſhop of London in the time of Wil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>liam the Conquerour.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Edward Barkham</hi> his Memo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rial of gratitude in commemo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ration of the ſaid Biſhop.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Raymond</hi> Arch-Deacon of St. Albans.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Bonham</hi> Son of Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas Bonham of Eſſex Eſq; and both of them anceſtors to the Bonhams of Hantſhire, whence Mr. Thomas Bonham of weſt<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mean in the ſaid County is pri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mogenially deſcended.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Northbury</hi> or Norbery Knight, keeper of the Garde<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>robe in the Tower of London, and anceſtor to the late John Norbery Eſq; Judge of South wales and father of George and John Norbery now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Owen</hi> the Epigrammatiſt.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Paganus</hi> de Roet father in Law to John of Gaunt Duke of Lancaſter.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gulielmus Green</hi> Doctor of Divi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nity.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gabriel Donne</hi> Doctor of Divi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nity.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Donne</hi> Dean of St. Pauls.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Alexander Nowel</hi> Dean of St. Pauls very antiently of Lan. and one of the branches of the Right honourable Baptiſt Lord Nowell viſcount Cambden of Cambden now living.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Simon Burley</hi> Knight of the Garter Warden of the Cinque ports.</item>
               <pb facs="tcp:45532:3"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Rogerus</hi> ſurnamed Niger Biſhop of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas</hi> de <hi>Eure</hi> Dean of St. Pauls a branch of the Right ho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nourable Lord Eure of Malton.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Simon Baskervile</hi> Knight M.D.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Wolley</hi> Knight, Secratary of ſtate to Queen <hi>Eliz.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Francis Wolley</hi> Knight his only ſon.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Collet</hi> Deane of St. Pauls ſon of Sir <hi>Henry Collet</hi> Knight, Lord Maior of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Acton</hi> of Acton in the County of Salop Eſq; Father in law to the worthy Sir Regi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nald Foſter Knight now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Ockford</hi> vicar of St. Faiths.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Simon Edolph</hi> of the County of Flint Eſq;</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>VVilliam Rythen</hi> Rector of St. Faiths.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Valantine Cary</hi> Dean of St. Pauls and Biſhop of Exon.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Newcourt</hi> Dean of the Col<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>legiat Church of Aukland.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ricardus Litchfield</hi> Arch-deacon of Middleſex.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Boyes</hi> of the County of Eſſex. Eſq;</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Nicholas Rickdel</hi> Eſq;</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Izabella</hi> wife of them both.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Petrus Gildenſtern</hi> Baron of Biſtrup one of the Daniſh nobi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lity.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Tomkins</hi> Batchelour of Muſick one of the antient and Knightly Family of the Tom<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kins in Herefordſhire, whereof the worthy Sir Thomas Tom<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kins of Monington upon Wye Kt. is Principall.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Beuchamp</hi> Knight of the Garter.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>VVilliam Earle</hi> of Pembrook, one of the moſt Noble ance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtors of the Right honourable Philip Earle of Pembrook, now living.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Nicholas Bacon</hi> Knight, keep<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>er of the Privy Seale, one of the anceſtors of that Knightly &amp; ſpreading Family of the Bacons in Suffolk, whence the late Na<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thaniel and Francis Bacon late of Grayes Inne were lineally deſcended.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robertus Benne</hi> de Newport Cranly, Gentleman.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Heneage</hi> Knight a moſt memorable Perſon in the Reign and Court of Qu. Eliz.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Linacre</hi> M.D. Phiſitian to Henry the eighth.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gulielmus Lilly</hi> firſt Maſter of St. Pauls ſchool.</item>
               <pb facs="tcp:45532:4"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas VVinterburne</hi> Dean of St, Pauls.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Mey</hi> or <hi>May</hi> Dean of St. Pauls.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Chateslehant</hi> Cannon of St. Pauls.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gulielmus Harrington</hi> one of the Cannon Reſidentaries of St. Pauls.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Fulco Baſſet</hi> Biſhop of London, one of that noble Family of the Baſſets in the County of Devon</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Nevil</hi> Lord Latimer one of the anceſtors of the noble Lord of Abergavanny firſt Ba<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ron of England.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Lacy</hi> Earl of Lincolne.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard</hi> de Graveſend Biſhop of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Hammon</hi> de Chickwell ſix times Maior of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Cheſhall</hi> Biſhop of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Reymundus Pelegrim</hi> Cannon of St. Pauls.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Munden</hi> Cannon of St. Pauls.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Munden</hi> Cannon of St. Pauls.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Fletcher</hi> Biſhop of Lon<g ref="char:EOLunhyphen"/>don, Father of the late Mr. Fletcher that famous Dramma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tique Poet.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Welford</hi> Arch Deacon of Colcheſter.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard de Placito</hi> Arch Deacon of Colcheſter.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richardus Newport</hi> Biſhop of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Rodolphus Baldock</hi> or Balduck Biſhop of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Stocksley</hi> Biſhop of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Bobert Breybrook</hi> Biſhop of Lon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>don and Chancellour of Eng<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>land.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Elmot</hi> Biſhop of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Fulco Lovell</hi> Arch deacon of Colcheſter.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John King</hi> Biſhop of London, Father to the Right Reverend and eminently learned John King Lord Biſhop of Chiche<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſter of a long ſtanding, deſcend<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ing from a very antient family in Devonſhire.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robertus Fitzhugh</hi> Biſhop of Lon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>don.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Margaret</hi> Counteſs of Shrewsbury.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Edward Boxhall</hi> Knight of the Garter.</item>
               <item>A very antient Tomb without any name, onely ſome frag<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ments of the inſcription are viſible.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Awbrey</hi> vicar Gen. to the Arch Biſhop of Canter<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bury
<pb facs="tcp:45532:4"/> one of the Progenitors of the honourable &amp; antient Fami<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ly of the Awbreys in Wales, and great Grandfather to ths Lady Mary Montague, daughter of the late Sir John Awbrey Knight, and wife of the truly honourable William Montague Atturney Generall to the Qu. of England, and brother to the Right honourable Edward Ba<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ron of Boughton.</item>
               <item>The Dutcheſs of Bedford ſiſter to Philip Duke of Burgondy.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Ralph</hi> de <hi>Hengham</hi> Lo. chief Juſtice of both Benches, one of the long-lind anceſtors of the Henghams, or Hevening<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ham in Norfolk, Knights from many generations, whence is lineally deſcended William Heveningham (Sonne and Heir of the late Sir Ralph) now liv<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ing</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Putney</hi> Knight Maior of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard</hi> de <hi>Pleſſeys</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Crofts</hi> Scout Maſter ge<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nerall of Ireland, and one of that antient and truly honoura<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ble Family of the Crofts in the County of Hereford &amp; Suffolk</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Kempe</hi> Biſhop of Lon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>don.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Edward Stanhop</hi> Knight vicar Gen. to the Arch-Biſhop of Canterbury, and one of that noble family of the Earle of Cheſterfield now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Ravis</hi> Biſhop of Lon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>don.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richardus Vaughan</hi> Biſhop of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richardus Periton</hi> Arch Deacon of Colcheſter.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Brian Walton</hi> Biſhop of Cheſter, and husband of Madam Anne Walton now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Barwick</hi> Dean of St. Pauls, and Brother to the worthy Do<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ctor Peter Barwick M.D C.L, now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Marcus Franck</hi> Arch Deacon of St. Albans.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Katharine</hi> third daughter of the late Edward Lord Nevil baron of Abergavanny.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Iles</hi> Eſq; publique no<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tary, one of the anceſtors to Mr. William Iles one of the principal attendants to the right Reverend George now Lord Biſhop of Winton.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Abney</hi> Reginae Camerarius.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>David Clapham</hi> Gen. one of the Proctors of the arches.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Cawood</hi> Stationer and Prin<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ter to Qu. Elizabeth.</item>
               <pb facs="tcp:45532:5"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Mollins</hi> Arch Deacon of London.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Elizabeth</hi> wife of the late Lord Schandols</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Brewſter</hi> Cannon of St. Pauls.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Margaret</hi> wife of Chriſtopher Robinſon.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John</hi> and <hi>Francis Aſtely</hi> Sonns of Sir John Aſtely Knight and Maſter of the Revells.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Weſt</hi> one of the Petty Cannons of St. Pauls.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Dockwray</hi> Notary, and one of the Proctors of the Arches.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Waterſon</hi> Stationer of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Simon Waterſon</hi> Stationer of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Francis Coldock</hi> Maſter of the Company of Stationers, all three the Progenitors of Mr. Simon Waterſon bookſeller late of St. Pauls Church yard yet living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Ironſide</hi> Stationer of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Norton</hi> Eſq; ſometime Stationer of London his Ne<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>phew.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Bonham Norton</hi> of Church-ſtret<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ton of the County of Salop Eſq; all three anceſtors to Arthur NortonEſq; Roger Norton Eſq; and John Norton of Lincolnes Inne Eſq; now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Petrus Osborne</hi> Eſq; remembran<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cer of the Exchequer father of the late Sir Peter Osborne Kt.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Mind</hi> of Salop Eſq;</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>George Whitgift</hi> Eſq;</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Lamb</hi> Eſq; ſervant to King Henry the 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Good</hi> one of the Petty Can<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nons of St. Pauls.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Babham</hi> and Alice Bur<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ton.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth</hi> wife of Robert Free<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Truſſel</hi> Eſq; grandchild of Sir Alured Truſſel of the Coun<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ty of Warwick Knight, and Father of the much honoured Collonel Edward Truſſel late of Pater Noſter Row, ſometimes High Sheriff of Hamſhire, which Collonel Edward is now living</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Higginſon</hi> Eſq; Alder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Lodowick Nichols</hi> of Northamp<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ton.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Johnſton</hi> one of the Pro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ctors of the Arches.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Alice Johnſton</hi> wife of the ſaid Robert.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Roger Hunt</hi> one of the Proctors of the Arches.</item>
               <pb n="1" facs="tcp:45532:5"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>David Dolben</hi> Biſhop of Bangor, of that antient Family of the Dolbens in Denbighſhire, from whence the Right Reverend Doctor John Dolben Dean of Weſtminſter, and Biſhop of Rocheſter is Lineally deſcend<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ed.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chriſtophorus Viſivicus</hi> Almoner to Henry the 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Thorsby</hi> of Thorsby in the County of York Eſq;</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Rowe</hi> Knight, Lord Maior of London.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Henry Rowe</hi> Knight, Sonne of Sir Thomas.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Nevill</hi> Lord Latimer.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Hanley</hi> Eſq;</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Banniſter</hi> Eſq; Sheriff and Alderman of London.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Anne Bulſtrode</hi> widdow of the ſaid John Banniſter.</item>
               <item>
                  <list>
                     <item>
                        <hi>Henry Daniel</hi>
                     </item>
                     <item>
                        <hi>Mary Daniel</hi>
                     </item>
                     <item>
                        <hi>Anne Daniel</hi>
                     </item>
                  </list> Brothers and Siſters.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Katharine Reynolds</hi> wife of Sir James Reynolds of Caſt<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lecomps in the County of Cam<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bridge.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Egmunton</hi> Rector of Hackney.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Mounſon</hi> Eſq; third Sonne of Sir John Mounſon of South-Carleton in the County of Lincoln Knight.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Harvey</hi> antiently of Foulkſton in the County of Kent Eſq; and one of the Pro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>genitors of the honourable Sir Daniel Harvey Knight, Biſhop of Comb park in the County of Surrey Knight and Baronet, now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Carew</hi> de Haccomb in the County of Devon, Eſq;</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richardus Forde</hi> Gen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>George Viner</hi> ſecond Sonne of the honourable Sir George Viner Knight and Baronet.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Etheldred Reynell</hi> daugh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ter and coheir of Sir George Peacock of Finchly Knight, &amp; wife of the late Sir George Reynell Knight, Marſhal of the Kings Bench.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James</hi> Lord <hi>Egerton</hi> viſcount Brackley.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Charles</hi> Lord <hi>Egerton</hi> viſcount Brackley.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Cecilia Egerton,</hi> all three the children of the Right ho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nourable John Lord Elleſmere viſcount Brackley, Earle of Bridgwater, and the Right ho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nourable the Lady Frances his Counteſs, daughter, and one of the coheirs of the Right ho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nourable Ferdinando Earle of Derby.</item>
               <pb n="2" facs="tcp:45532:6"/>
               <item>Mrs. <hi>Katharine Currance</hi> wife of Mr. Allan Currance, anceſtors to the truly worthy John Currance Eſq; now liv<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ing.</item>
               <item>Mrs. <hi>Dorothy Sewell</hi> wife of Robert Sewell Eſq; Draper of Lonndon.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Martin Nowell</hi> Knight, deſcend<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ed from that antient and ho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nourable Family of the Nowels in Lancaſhire, and father to the truly honoured Sir Martin Nowel Knight B. now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas</hi> Lord <hi>Coventry</hi> Keeper of the great Seale of England anceſtor to the flouriſhing and honourable Family of the Co<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ventries now living.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Alan Apsly</hi> Knight, Leive<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tenant of the Tower, Father of the worthily honoured Sir Alan Apſly Knight &amp;c. Comp<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>troler to his moſt illuſtrious Highneſs James Duke of York.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Howard</hi> Earle of Arun<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dell and Surrey one of the an<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ceſtours to the illuſtrious Fa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mily of the Duke of Norfolk, now living.</item>
               <item>Lord <hi>Thomas Darcy</hi> of the North one of the anceſtours to the honourable Sir William Darcy and Edward Darcy now living.</item>
               <item>Lord <hi>John Paslay</hi> sonne of the Earle of Abercrome, husband of the honourable Lady Katha<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rine Lenthall one of the daugh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ters of Sir John Lenthall Kt. ſtylo veteri, and Marſhall of the Kings Bench.</item>
               <item>Lord <hi>Thomas Egerton</hi> Baron of Elleſmere Lord high Chan<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cellour of England, ance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtour to the Right honourable the Earle of Bridgwater now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William</hi> Lord <hi>Compton</hi> his armes one of the anceſtours of the Right honourable the Earle of Northampton now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward</hi> Lord <hi>Bruce</hi> Baron of Kinloſſe, one of the Princely Progenitours of the Right ho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nourable and eminently noble Edward Earle of Alisbury and Earle of Elgin now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Radcliff</hi> Earle of Suſſex one of the anceſtors to the Right honourable the Earle of Suſſex now living.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Elizabeth</hi> late Counteſs Dowager of Exeter, buried in St. James Clarkenwel.</item>
               <item>Lord Biſhop <hi>q Fotherby</hi> buried in Alhallows Lumbardſtreet
<pb n="3" facs="tcp:45532:6"/> with a magnificent Tomb o<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ver him.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Dom. Johannes Epiſcopus Ba<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thoniae &amp; Wellen.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Marſhal</hi> Earl of Pem<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>broke.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Marſhal</hi> his ſon, Earl of Salisbury.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Lionel Cranfeild</hi> Earl of Mid<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dleſex, anceſtor to the Right honourable Earl of Middle<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſex now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Margareta Comitiſſa de Sa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lop.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Catharine Nevil</hi> Coun<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>teſs of Rutland.</item>
               <item>Lord <hi>Thomas Millington</hi> Ba<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ron of Weemes.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Grizald Windſor,</hi> ſole daughter of the L. Windſor.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Elizabeth Bruges,</hi> wife of the Lord Chandois.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Ma.</hi> Counteſs of Hun<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tington.</item>
               <item>The Counteſs of <hi>Worceſter,</hi> in Garlick-hithe-Church.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Holland</hi> Duke of Exe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ter.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Anne Stafford</hi> Dut<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cheſs of Exeter</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Anne Mountague</hi> Dut<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cheſs of Exeter.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Conſtance Holland,</hi> ſi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſter of the ſaid Duke of Ex<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>eter.</item>
               <item>Lord <hi>Francis Butler,</hi> or <hi>Bote<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ler.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Randulphus Brownrigge Epiſc. Exon Lond.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Michael Blount</hi> lieut. of the Tower.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Richard Blount</hi> Knight, lieut. of the Tower.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Allen Apſley</hi> Knight, lieut. of the Tower, anceſtor to Sir <hi>Allen Apſley</hi> Knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Parkhurſt</hi> Knight, Comptroller of the Mint.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Edw. Devereux</hi> Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Nicholas Carew</hi> Knight of the Garter, and anceſtor to the now ſir Nicholas Carew of Beddington.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Pelham</hi> Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Edw. Darcy</hi> ſon of the Lo. <hi>Darcy.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Deddham</hi> Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Edward Barkham</hi> Knight, Lo. M. anceſtor to the now ſir Robert and ſir Edward Barkham Baronets.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Paul Pindar</hi> Knight, and anceſtor to Matthew Pindar Eſq; one of the fix Clerks.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Anne Gib,</hi> wife to the late ſir Henry Gib of Scot<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>land Baronet, and daughter of the yet living ſir Ralph Gibbs of Honnington in
<pb n="4" facs="tcp:45532:7"/> Warwick-ſhire.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Ambroſe Charcam</hi> Knight</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Cardina Schoder,</hi> wife of ſir Richard Schoder Kt.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Crosby</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, builder and firſt ow<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ner of Crosby houſe.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Tho. Greſham</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Nicholas Rainton</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Pickering</hi> Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Pickering</hi> Knight, both anceſtors to ſir Gilbert Pickering of Northampt. and of ſir Henry Pickering of Cambridge-ſhire, both Ba<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ronets, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Spencer</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Holles</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior, anceſtor to the three laſt ſucceſſive Earls of Clare.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Julius Caeſar</hi> Knight, Ma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſter of the Rolls, anceſtor to ſir Henry Caeſar of the coun<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ty of Hertf.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Langham</hi> Knight and Baronet, father of the emi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nently learned ſir James Langham Knight, his Vault.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>George VVhitmore</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, father of Wil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>liam Whitmore of B. Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Milburne</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>VVilliam Cheſter</hi> Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Branch</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Hellena Branch</hi> his wife.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Stephen Slanie</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Hart</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>George Bolles</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, anceſtor to the now ſir John Bolles of Scampton, Baronet.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Ralph Jocelyn</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Rivers</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Robert Chichely</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Rowland Hill</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Leigh</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, anceſtor to Edward Leigh of Glouceſter Eſq;</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Stephen Cavendiſh</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Baldry</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Bennet</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior, anceſtor to ſir Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas Bennet of Babraham in
<pb n="5" facs="tcp:45532:7"/> the county of Cambridge, Baronet; and ſir Humphry Bennet of Hants, Knight and Colonel.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Edward Shaw</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Lock</hi> Knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Aleyn</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, one of the Privie Council to Hen. 8. anceſtor to the now ſir George Aleyn of Eſſex, and ſir Thomas Aleyn of London, Knight and Baronet.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Pope</hi> Knight, Trea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſurer of the Augmentati<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ons.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>George Bond</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Godfrey Bullen,</hi> or <hi>Bollen,</hi> anceſtor to Anne Bullen, mo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther of Queen Elizabeth of famous memory.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Samuel Mico</hi> his Hatch<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ment.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Edward Aker</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Ralph Warren</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Lyons</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Iken</hi> Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Martin Bowes</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Ramſey</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Alice Ramſey,</hi> his La<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dy.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Mary Ramſey,</hi> his La<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dy.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Simon Ayres</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Hugh Brice</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Arundel</hi> Knight of the Bath, and Knight-Banne<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ret.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Percival</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Thomaſin Percival,</hi> his Lady.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Richard Payne</hi> Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Brugge,</hi> or <hi>Bruges,</hi> of Dimmock in Glouceſter<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſhire, Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>George Stanley</hi> Knight of the Garter, ſon of the Lord Strange, anceſtors of the now Earl of Derby.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Roger Jones</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Gore</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, anceſtor to that Knightly family of the Gores in the county of Herts.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Gore</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Mary Brook,</hi> daughter
<pb n="6" facs="tcp:45532:8"/> to the Lord Brook, one of the Barons of the Exche<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>quer.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Catharine Killigrew,</hi> one of that moſt ancient and ho<g ref="char:EOLunhyphen"/>nourable family of the Killi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>grews in Cornwal.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Gizors</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Ralph Aſtry</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, anceſtor to the <hi>Aſtries</hi> of Woodend in the county of Bedf.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Cutbert Hacket</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Stephen Spilman</hi> Knight, Sheriff and Chamberlain of London, one of the branches of that long-flouriſhing fa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mily of the Spilmans in Nor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>folk.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Rich. Whittington</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Richard Marlow</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Bayly</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Lodge</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Laxton</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Richard Maddox</hi> Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Henry Kybel,</hi> or <hi>Kyble,</hi> knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Roger Martin</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Knowles</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Craven</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, anceſtor to the Right honourable and truly Noble Lord William Cra<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ven, Baron of Hemſted, and Earl of Craven.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Nich. Farringdon</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, from whom Farringdon-Ward took its denomination.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Munde</hi> Goldſmith, Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Alexander Avenon</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Chriſtopher Askew,</hi> or <hi>Aſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cough,</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Henry Fitz-alwin</hi> Knight, Maior, and Maior intermiſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſively four and twenty years together.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Bowyer</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Hubblethorne</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Stephen Jennings</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Ralph Freeman</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Capel</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior, one of the anceſtors
<pb n="7" facs="tcp:45532:8"/> to the now Earl of Eſſex.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Anne Awnſham,</hi> Lady of the late ſir <hi>Gideon Awn<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſham</hi> Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Walter Knight</hi> of Canter<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bury.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Garway</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, anceſtor to Hen Garway of Ford in Suſſex Eſq;</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Nicholas Gold</hi> Baronet, late husband to the Lady Gold, now wife of Thomas Neal of Warmford Eſq;</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Rowland Heyward</hi> Knight, twice Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Glover</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Daniel</hi> Knight, one of the Judges of the C.P.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Hugh Wyche</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Grizald Tuke,</hi> wife of ſir Brian Tuke Knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> and one of the anceſtors of ſir Samuel Tuke knight and Colonel.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Leigh</hi> knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Edmund Bacon</hi> knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Hayes</hi> knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Swinnerton</hi> knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>VVilliam Stone</hi> knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Cheke,</hi> (moſt ancient<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ly <hi>Cheque</hi>) tutor to <hi>Edward</hi> the ſixth.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Cheke</hi> knight, his Granchild; both anceſtors to Robert Cheke of Pergoe in Eſſex Eſq; <hi>&amp;c.</hi> and Thomas Cheke his brother, one of the Eſquires of his Majeſties body, and one of the Ca<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ptains of his Majeſties Guard.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Henry VVeever,</hi> or <hi>VVea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ver,</hi> knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John VVoodcock</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Simon d'Ewes</hi> of Gelder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>land, knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>James Yerford</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Robert Ducy</hi> knight, Lord Maior, one of the anceſtors to that learned man, and great lover of learned men, ſir William Ducy of Froſter in the County of Glouceſter Knight-Baronet, and of ſir Hugh Ducie knight of the Bath.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Greſham</hi> knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Aliffe</hi> knight, ance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtor
<pb n="8" facs="tcp:45532:9"/> to ſir <hi>Benjamin Aliffe</hi> in the county of Eſſex.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>VVolſtan Dixy</hi> knight, Lo. Maior, anceſtor to ſir Wool<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtan Dixy of Market-Boſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>worth in the county of Lei<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ceſter, Knight-Baronet.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Darcy</hi> knight, ſon of the Lord Darcy.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Grizald Windſour,</hi> daughter to the Lord Wind<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſour.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Rumny.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Humphry Weld</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior, one of the anceſtors to Humphry Weld of Lul<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>worth-Caſtle, Eſq; and ſir John Weld Knight, his younger brother.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Cambel</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Cambel</hi> his ſon, Alder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>James Cambel</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior, Grandchild of the ſair ſir Thomas.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Hewit</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior, Batchelor.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Wroth</hi> of Pether<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ly-Park in the county of So<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>merſet, Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Martin Nowel</hi> knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Henry Anderſon</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Richard Gurney</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Michael Dormer</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, anceſtor to the late ſir Robert Dormer of Dourton in the county of Buckingham, knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Humphry Starkey</hi> knight, Baron of the Exchequer.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Margaret Erlington,</hi> daughter and heir of Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas Lord Itchingham.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Edward Mulſhew</hi> knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Oldhall</hi> knight.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>K. Kyme.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Heir Tank,</hi> or <hi>Haretan<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cleux,</hi> an Almain, Knight of the Garter.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Cootes</hi> knight, Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Finknel</hi> knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>James Hawes</hi> knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Richard Morgan</hi> knight, Lord Chief Juſtice of the Common Pleas.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Mitchel</hi> knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Poultney</hi> knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Poultney</hi> knight, Lo. Maior, from whom <hi>S.</hi> Law<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rence Poultney's Church took her denomination.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Guil. Booth,</hi> eldeſt ſon of ſir
<pb n="9" facs="tcp:45532:9"/> George, now Lord Booth Baron of Delamere.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Jo. Thorowgood</hi> of Hodeſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>den in the county of Hertf. Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>George Strode,</hi> knight, long ſince Colonel, and father of ſir Nicholas Strode of Kent knight and Baronet, and of Colonel Strode Governour of Dover.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Elizab. Bercklay,</hi> wife of the late ſir Maurice Berck<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lay, Knight.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Iſabella Sackvile,</hi> Prio<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>reſs of Clerkenwel.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Weſton</hi> Knight, Prior of S. Johns of Jeruſa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lem.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Walter Manny,</hi> or <hi>de Mey<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nie,</hi> Knight.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Elizabeth Aſcough.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Henry Grey,</hi> ſon of the late George Earl of Kent.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Anne Strange.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Hawly</hi> Knight, Clarencieux, and anceſtor to James Hawly of Brainford, Eſq; <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Conſtance Lucy</hi> of Charlecot in the County of Warwick.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Wriotheſly</hi> Knight, King at Arms, and anceſtor to the late Thomas Earl or Southampton.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Elizabeth Richardſon,</hi> wife of the now ſir Thomas Lord Richardſon.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Anne Packington.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>George Dalſton</hi> of Dalſton in the county of Cumber<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>land, Baronet, father of the now ſir William Dalſton Ba<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ronet of the ſame Lord<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſhip.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Catharine Beaumont.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Catharine Mountague.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Elizabeth Puckering,</hi> daughter of ſir John Mor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ley of Suff. Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>George Curſon</hi> Knight, and father-in-law to the late Ed<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ward Earl of Dorſet.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Frances Trevors,</hi> wife of ſir Thomas Trevors.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Prudence Trevor.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Edward Philips</hi> Knight, Maſter of the Rolls, his arms in that Chappel; an<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ceſtor to <hi>Edward Philips</hi> of the county of Somerſet Eſq; Knight of the ſhire; and Col. Robert Philips of the Bed-chamber.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Harbottle Grimſton</hi> of <gap reason="illegible: omitted in print" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> in the county of Eſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſex, Knight-Baronet, Maſter
<pb n="10" facs="tcp:45532:10"/> of the Rolls; whoſe arms are in the window.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Viner</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior, anceſtor to the now ſir George Viner Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Chriſtoph. Clithero</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, anceſtor to James Clithero, and Henry Clithero, Eſquires.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Chriſtopher Minns</hi> Knight, one of the great Comman<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ders at ſea.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Anthony Sentleger</hi> Knight.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Ellinor Sentleger,</hi> wife of ſir Anthony.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Aſhburnham</hi> Knight, one of the ancienteſt fami<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lies in the kingdom, and one of the anceſtors to the ho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nourable Colonel John Aſh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>burnham; both of his late and preſent Majeſties Bed-chamber.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Richard Hutton</hi> Knight, one of the Juſtices, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Walter Mildmay</hi> Knight, Privie Counſellor to Queen Eliz. and one of the ance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtors, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Eastfield</hi> knight of the Bath, Lord Maior, who built the Conduit in Fleetſtreet.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Margaret North,</hi> wife of Edward Lord North.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Rowe</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Alice Avenon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Baptist Hicks</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior, anceſtor to the Lord Viſcount Campden.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Jeoffry Feilding</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, anceſtor to the now Earl of Denbigh and Deſmond.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Godfrey Bullen,</hi> or <hi>Bollen;</hi> one of the ſons of Sir God<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>frey, buried in Mercers Chap<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>pel.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Anne Bromely,</hi> wife of ſir John Bromely Knight.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Elizab. Jhones,</hi> wife of ſir Francis Jhones Knight.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Mary Swift,</hi> wife of ſir Francis Swift of Naſing in the county of Eſſex, knight, and daughter of Fra. Wa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>terhouſe Eſq; and Bridget his wife, both the father and mother of the now Edward Waterhouſe of Greenford in the county of Middleſex, Eſq;</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Bartholoew Reade</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Edmund Wright</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, father to the Lady <hi>Harrington</hi> wife of ſir
<pb n="11" facs="tcp:45532:10"/> James; and the Lady Pig<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>got, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Cordel</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, anceſtor to ſir Ro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bert Cordel of Long Mel<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ford in the county of Nor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>folk, Baronet.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Burgoine</hi> Knight, anceſtor to the Knightly fa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mily of the Burgoines in the county of Bedford.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Nicholas Twiford</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>James Pemberton</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>James Drax</hi> Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>James Drax</hi> Knight, his ſon, father and brother of Henry Drax Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Jane Thorpe,</hi> wife of ſir Thomas Thorpe Knight, Ba<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ron of the Exchequer.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Walter Blount</hi> Knight of the Garter.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Margaret Ramſey,</hi> that moſt munificent Benefa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ctreſs.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Venetia Digby,</hi> wife of the late honourable ſir Ke<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nelm Digby, Knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Philpot,</hi> or <hi>Philipot,</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, ance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtor to the worthy and Knightly family of the Phi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lipots in the county of Hants.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Allen Chenie</hi> Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Chriſtopher Edmonds</hi> Kt. Privie Counſellor to Queen Elizabeth.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Eliz. Edmonds,</hi> his wife.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Gurney,</hi> wife of Rob. South, Goldſmith, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Edward Mansfield</hi> Baro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>net.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Stephen Foſter</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Henry Baynton</hi> Knight, Treaſurer to the Chamber of Hen. 8. and one of the anceſtors of that anciently Knightly and opulent family of the Bayntons of Bromhal in the county of Wilts.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Ridley</hi> knight, Do<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ctor of the Civil law, Chan<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cellor of Winton, and Vicar-general to the then Archbi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſhop of Canterbury, father to the late Anne Boſvile, and Elizabeth, wife of Mark Cottel Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Ambroſe Nichols</hi> Knight, <hi>q.</hi> if not Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Chadworth,</hi> or <hi>Shad<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>worth,</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Cutbert Barnes</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <pb n="12" facs="tcp:45532:11"/>
               <item>Sir <hi>Nicholas Criſpe</hi> Knight-Ba<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ronet and Colonel, and fa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther to the now ſir Nicholas Criſpe of Hammerſmith, Ba<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ronet, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Pargiter</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, anceſtor to that worthy family of the Pargi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ters in Northampton-ſhire, whence Mr. Pargiter, Gold<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſmith, is lineally deſcended.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Robert Chichly</hi> knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Allot</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Olyffe</hi> Knight, She<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>riff.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Allen Cotton</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Hewit</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Walworth</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Lovekin,</hi> four times Maior, and Maſter of ſir William Walworth.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Henry Amcots</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Leman</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, anceſtor to ſir Willi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>am Leman of Northal in the county of Herts, Knight and Baronet.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Dormer</hi> knight, Lord Maior, one of the an<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ceſtors to the now Charles Earl of Carnarvon.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Robert Denny</hi> knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Hugh Hammerſly</hi> knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Offley</hi> knight, Lord Maior, anceſtor to that wor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thy family of the Offleys in Stafford-ſhire.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Elizabeth Whitmore,</hi> Lady-mother to the now ſir William Whitmore of Shrop<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſhire Baronet, and his bro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther ſir Thomas, knight of the Bath.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Nicholas Throckmorton</hi> kt. ſeveral times Embaſſadour from Queen Elizabeth.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Geere</hi> knight, ance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtor to the now ſir Robert Geere Knight-Ba.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Samuel Owfeild,</hi> or <hi>Ould<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>field,</hi> knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Flemming</hi> knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Hawkins</hi> knight, the famous Sea-commander in Queen Elizabeths Reign.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Bartholomew James</hi> knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Chriſtopher Draper</hi> knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Web</hi> knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <pb n="13" facs="tcp:45532:11"/>
               <item>Lady <hi>Bennet,</hi> daughter of ſir Chriſtopher Draper.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Richard Champion</hi> knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Lawſon</hi> knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> four of his children.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Blanck</hi> knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Margaret Blanck,</hi> his wife.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Cutbert Buckle</hi> knight, an<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ceſtor to ſir Chriſtopher Buc<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kle knight; and both to Lieut. Col. Buckle of Bur<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rough neer Bamſted-downs.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Robert Hampſon</hi> knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Curteene</hi> knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Richard Tate</hi> Knight, and an Embaſſadour from King Hen. 8.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Test,</hi> knight of the holy Sepulchre.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Henry Billingſley</hi> knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Elizabeth Billingſley</hi> his wife.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>David Doeringck</hi> knight.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Mary Heigham,</hi> daugh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ter of ſir <hi>John Colt.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Arthur Savage</hi> knight, Ge<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>neral of Queen Eliz. her for<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ces for France.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Tho. Mellington</hi> Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Richard Rice</hi> Knight, be<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>headed on Tower-hill.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Skevington</hi> Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Aſſeldy</hi> Knight, ſub-Marſhal of England.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Anne Clarke,</hi> wife of the now ſir Francis Clarke late of Exeter.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Stanly,</hi> wife of ſir Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas Stanly, daughter of ſir Roger Appleton Knight-Ba<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ronet.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>James Deane</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Radclyffe</hi> Knight, ſon of the late Robert Earl of Suſſex.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Anne,</hi> wife of ſir John Radclyffe.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Richard Haddon</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Catharine,</hi> wife of Al<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>derman Stoakes.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Lenthal</hi> Knight, Knight-Marſhal of the Kings Bench; a fair Table for him and his neer relations.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Etheldred Reynell,</hi> wife of ſir George Reynel, Knight-Marſhal, and daughter of Sir Edw. Peacock of Finchly Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Manners</hi> Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Seymour</hi> Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Leigh</hi> Knight.</item>
               <pb n="14" facs="tcp:45532:12"/>
               <item>Dame <hi>Margaret St. John,</hi> wife of ſir Alexander St. John of Bletſoe.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Lovel</hi> knight of the Garter.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Erlington</hi> Knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>George Haſtings</hi> Knight, ſon of the late Lord Ha<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtings.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Edmond Osborne</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Portman</hi> Knight, Lord Chief Juſtice of Eng<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>land, one of the long-lin'd anceſtors of the now ſir Wil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>liam Portman of Orchard, Baronet, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Coventry</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Joane Dethick.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Margaret,</hi> daughter of ſir Ralph Chenie.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Matthew Boynton</hi> Baro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>net.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Blackwel</hi> knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Matthew Carew</hi> of Corn<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>wal Knight, one of the an<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ceſtors to George Carew of Richmond Eſq; and one of his Majeſties Privie Cham<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ber.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Roger Cholmely</hi> knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Ralph Winwood</hi> Knight, Secretary of Eſtate to King James, and one of the an<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ceſtors of Ralph Winwood of Quainton in Bucking<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ham-ſhire, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Anne Bodely,</hi> wife of the late ſir Thomas Bodely.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Chriſtopher Wandesford,</hi> one of the anceſtors to that worthy family of the Wan<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>desfords in Yorkſhire.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Richard Mallory</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Gerrard,</hi> or <hi>Gar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rard,</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Garrard,</hi> ſir Willi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ams grandchilde.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>M. Slanies</hi> arms in a window.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Middleton</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Barceter</hi> knight.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Robert Chamberlaine,</hi> alias <hi>Tankevile,</hi> knight of the Bath, anceſtor of that knight<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ly family of the Chamber<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lains, <hi>alias</hi> Tankeviles in the county of Oxford.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Anne Littleton,</hi> wife of the late ſir Edw. Littleton.</item>
               <item>The Lady <hi>Browne,</hi> late wife of the now ſir Richard Browne, Knight and Baronet, and Major-General of all the Militia of London.</item>
               <pb n="15" facs="tcp:45532:12"/>
               <item>Lady <hi>Margaret Talbot.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Malefant</hi> Knight, one of the Barons of the Exchequer.</item>
               <item>The Lady <hi>Adams,</hi> wife of the learned, and true lover of learning, the honourable ſir Thomas Adams, Knight-Ba<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ronet, and father of the City,</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Jaſper Cleyton</hi> knight, She<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>riff, very anciently of Oa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kenſhaw in the county of York; father of the worthi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ly honoured Sir John Cley<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ton Knight, and Mr. George Cleyton Mercer of Lon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>don.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>George Garret,</hi> Knight and Alderman.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Adler</hi> Knight, buried at <hi>S.</hi> Gregories.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>J. Rumny</hi> Knight, buried in <hi>S.</hi> Magnus Church.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Hugh Brawne</hi> knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Fowler</hi> knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Fiſher</hi> Baronet, an<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ceſtor to the now ſir Thomas Fiſher of Iſlington Knight-Baronet.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Nicholas Kempe</hi> knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Sarah Kempe,</hi> his wife.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Robert Holbourne</hi> knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Collins</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Pope</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Pexall</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Anne Jones.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Freind.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chriſtopher Rawſon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Collins.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth Bloſs.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Nathaniel Snape</hi> Eſq; father of <hi>Grays Inne</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chriſtopher Gold</hi> Eſq;,</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Peter Wentworth</hi> Eſq; ance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtor to Sir Peter Wentworth of Oxfordſhire; an ancient Knight of the Bath.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Samuel Payler</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mary Payler,</hi> his wife.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Aſcough</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Agges,</hi> one of the War<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ders of the Tower.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Agnes Bond,</hi> wife of the late William Bond, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Anne Andrews.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Jacobus Zambone,</hi> Agent for the Repub. of Venice.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Polſted</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Barba Thornix.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Hieronymus Benalius.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Armorer</hi> of Nor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thumb. Eſq; Governor to the Pages of Honour of Hen. 8. and anceſtor to Sir William and Sir Nicholas Armorer,
<pb n="16" facs="tcp:45532:13" rendition="simple:additions"/> Knights, and neer kinſmen, <hi>Radulphus Darling.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Baldwine Hamey</hi> Eſq; M.D. chief Phyſician to the great Duke of Muſcovia, and fa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther to the moſt eminently learned, and exemplarily li<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>beral, Dr. Baldwin Hamey M.D. C.L.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Roger Hatton</hi> Eſq; Alderman.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Frances Goldſmith,</hi> daughter of Sir Francis Appleton Knight and Baronet.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Nicholas Bremiſgrave</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Francis Covell</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Catharine Covell</hi> his wife.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Vyrby.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Roberts.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Tho. Catayii.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Bacon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Burnel.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mary Burnel.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth Denham,</hi> wife of William Denham, Merchant of the Staple.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>George Snayth</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Thinne</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Tull.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Roger Jones.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Francis Cherry.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Philip Dennis</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Tilling.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Robinſon</hi> Alderman.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Jane Ruſſel,</hi> of the Pri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vie Chamber to Queen Eli<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>zabeth.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Conſtance Lucie.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Jar. Martun</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henricus Nowellus.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Judith Megges,</hi> wife of William Meggs, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Meggs</hi> Eſq; father of William Meggs of London Eſq; and Dr. James Meggs Doctor of Divinity, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Conſtance Alford.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mary Evans,</hi> wife to Phil. E<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vans.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Roſſe</hi> Draper.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Haſſal</hi> Gent ſon of the late Dr. Haſſal, Chaplain to the Queen of Bohemia.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Abigail Jones.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Carre.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Samuel Saunders.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Kant.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Suſanna Duke.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Suſan Bennet,</hi> wife of Roger Bennet.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Rob. Taylor de Sylverdail,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>David Belgay,</hi> or <hi>Balgay,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Alice Carpenter.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Dove</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Belliniam</hi> of Erring<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ham, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Tiril</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <pb n="17" facs="tcp:45532:13"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Tutchin</hi> Eſq; Deputy of his Ward.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Hugo Wickstead.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Heſter Eſſington,</hi> daughter of Mr. William Eſſington, Mer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chant.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Cocks</hi> Citizen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Redman,</hi> Rector of S. Botolphs Biſhops-gate.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Georgius Brigges Armig. Ca<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>pitaneus.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Bond</hi> Eſquire, She<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>riff and Alderman of Lon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>don.</item>
               <item>Captain <hi>Martin Bond</hi> his ſon; both immediate anceſtors to the moſt obliging William Bond Eſq; and Alderman of London, now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Greſham</hi> Eſq; ſon of the famous Sir Thomas Gre<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſham Knight.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Adam Lawrence</hi> Gent. Mer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chant, Nephew to the hono<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rable Sir John Lawrence, Knight and Baronet, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Joane de Bovehii.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Martin.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gulielmus Bently.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Abrahamus Aurelius.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Wartenis.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Kerwin</hi> Citizen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Valentine Moretoft</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Suzan.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Walter Briggin.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Robinſon</hi> Merchant.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Christian Robinſon</hi> his wife.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Cornelius Linckebeck</hi> a Dutch Merchant.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Owen Saimpeire.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Staper</hi> Eſq; Alder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man, and a memorable Mer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chant.</item>
               <item>Captain <hi>Lewis Roberts.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Dreux,</hi> Doctor of Divinity.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Clemence Langley,</hi> wife of <hi>Richard Langley.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Pincen,</hi> Draper.</item>
               <item>Mr. <hi>William Vincent</hi> his chil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dren.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chriſtopher Tolderney,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Graffan,</hi> Grocer.</item>
               <item>Mr <hi>Hawes.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Rebecca Criſpe,</hi> wife of the late Sir Nicholas Criſpe, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Walker,</hi> Vintner.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizaheth Thomas.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Caecilia Aſhford,</hi> of the county of Devon.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Nathaniel Temnes,</hi> Eſq; Al<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>derman.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Nordell.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Shute,</hi> Architect.</item>
               <item>Mr. <hi>
                     <gap reason="illegible: omitted in print" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                        <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                     </gap> Hawes,</hi> Watch<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>maker.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Montague,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <pb n="18" facs="tcp:45532:14"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gilbert Melites.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chriſtian Melites.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Francis Barneham</hi> Eſq; She<g ref="char:EOLunhyphen"/>riff.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Benedict Barneham,</hi> Eſq; an<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ceſtor to the now Sir Robert Barneham of Boughton in Kent, Baronet, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Randal Manning,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Eartholomew Barnes,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Walter Plummer,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Rogers.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Southwel,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Rogerus Fenton,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Dunſtable,</hi> idem.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edoardus Lupton,</hi> idem.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Oliver Style,</hi> Eſq; Alderman, of that ſpreading &amp; Knight<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ly family of the Styles in Kent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Kirby,</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Scot</hi> of Hawlden in Kent, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Ailworth,</hi> Grocer.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Saxton.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Iken,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Suſan Lewen.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Kirby.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Norton,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Cavendiſh,</hi> Eſq; She<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>riff.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Humphry Baskervile,</hi> Eſq; She<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>riff.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Rich,</hi> Eſq; ſon of Ri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chard Rich, both Sheriffs and Aldermen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Browne</hi> and <hi>Fiſhbourne.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Barnes,</hi> Mercer and Maior.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Hawley,</hi> Mercer and Maior.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Huiſh,</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mary Muffet,</hi> his wife.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Anne Nevet,</hi> wife of Mr. Ed. Nevet of Cony-hatch in the County of Middleſex, Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Hall</hi> of Grays Inne, Eſq; that compil'd the Chro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nicle, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Anne Farrar,</hi> daughter of William Shephard of great Rowbright.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Catharine Prettiman.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Catherine Philips,</hi> the great Sappho of our age.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Gloceſter,</hi> Eſq; Alder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Randal.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Sugar Piſcenarius.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Bernard Randolph,</hi> Eſq; City-Sergeant.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Herbert Randolph,</hi> Eſq;</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gulielmus Drury,</hi> Doctor of Laws, and Judge of the Pre<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rogative-court.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Margaret Snell.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Captain <hi>Halſey,</hi> &amp;c.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>George Coleman,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <pb n="19" facs="tcp:45532:14"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Alice Coleman,</hi> his wife, and daughter of George Gainſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ford, Eſq; ſon of Sir John Gainsford of Crowhurſt, Knight.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>R. Wilcox,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Woodroffe,</hi> Merchant-Taylor.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mary Sandys,</hi> wife of Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas Sandys, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes de Rothing,</hi> a great Benefactor to, if not Builder of Queenhithe.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Walter Neale,</hi> Eſq; Sheriff <hi>anno</hi> 1352.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard de Lyon,</hi> Armig. She<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>riff.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Plat,</hi> Eſq; Sheriff, anceſtor to that worthy fa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mily of the Plats now li<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ving.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edmund Chapman,</hi> Eſq; ſer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vant to Queen Elizabeth.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Jaſper Draper,</hi> Eſq; Alder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gerrard Gore,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Judge <hi>Philip Jermin</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Suſanna le Porce.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Foy.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Cornwallis</hi> Eſq; She<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>riff.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Petrus de la Genebra.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Stokesby.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Micolt,</hi> or <hi>Mico,</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Radolphus Aſtry,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Wilſon,</hi> Maſter of the Bridge-houſe.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Billidge,</hi> Silk-dyer.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richardus Hill,</hi> Maſter of the Wine-cellar to H 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Farrington,</hi> or <hi>Far<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ringdon,</hi> Alderman.</item>
               <item>Dr <hi>John Dove,</hi> Doctor of Di<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vinity, ſometimes Rector of S. Mary Aldermanbury, and anceſtor to the much worthy John Dove of Grays Inne, I.C. now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ralph Holland</hi> Eſq;. Sheriff.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Narberry</hi> Eſq; Judge of South-Wales, father to Mr George and Mr John Nor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>berry, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Chaucer,</hi> Vintner, fa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther to Sir Geoffry Chau<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cer.</item>
               <item>Dr <hi>William Harvey,</hi> M.D. the famous Phyſician of his time.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Taylor</hi> Eſq; Sheriff.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Pluckenett,</hi> Merchant-Taylor.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Welles,</hi> a memorable Ci<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tizen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Symond Street.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Dauntſey</hi> Eſq; Al<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>derman, one of the ance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtors of Sir John Dauntſey
<pb n="20" facs="tcp:45532:15"/> of Laverſtock in the Coun<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ty of Wilts.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ade de Buck.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Lambert.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Humphry Walcot,</hi> Eſq; ance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtor to the flouriſhing fami<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ly of the Walcots of Wal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cot in the County of Salop.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Philemon Holland,</hi> of the ſame family as Dr Philemon Hol<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>land of Coventry, M.D.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Blanckworth.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edmond Crich,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edmond Crich, filius.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Allen,</hi> Eſq; Sheriff, Alderman, one of the ance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtors of the honourable Sir Thomas Allen of Finchly, Knight; and one of the Knights of the Shire for the County of Middleſex.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Auguſtine Hinde,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Prannel,</hi> Eſq; Sheriff.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Alkin.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gilbert Errington,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Cropley</hi> Eſq; Alder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man, and anceſtor of the honourable Sir John Crop<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ley, Knight and Baronet.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Banks,</hi> Eſq; Alderman, Deputy of Baſing-Hall-Ward.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Dogget,</hi> Eſq; Sheriff, Al<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>derman.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William de Avenger.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Lancelot Bathurst</hi> Eſq; Al<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>derman, and anceſtor to Edward Bathurſt, Eſq; and Alderman, now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John West,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Francis Bowyer</hi> of Chicheſter, Eſq; Alderman.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Hall,</hi> Draper.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Carolus Hawkins,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Elizabeth Huſſey.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Cooper,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Markes.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Meſſe.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Weſtrop,</hi> or <hi>Weſtrow.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Judith Fowler.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Taylor,</hi> Draper.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Alexander Evering.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Francis Bennenſon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mary Caldwel.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Hugh Dawſet.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Barnes.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Roberts.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Trygon,</hi> Eſq; Merchant.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Kendrick,</hi> a moſt me<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>morable Citizen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Pike,</hi> Alderman.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Craſhaw,</hi> Goldſmith.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Drew.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Lemot,</hi> Eſq; Alderman.</item>
               <item>Dr <hi>Thomas Harriot,</hi> Doctor of Divinity.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Peter Tryon,</hi> Eſq; anceſtor to Sir Peter Tryon of South-Halſted
<pb n="21" facs="tcp:45532:15"/> in the county of Eſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſex, Knight-B.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Beecher</hi> Eſq; Alderman, one of the anceſtors to that worthy family of the Bee<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chers in the County of Bed<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ford.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Margaret Hill,</hi> wife of Dr Hill, Doctor of Divinity.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Walter Knight</hi> of Canterbu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ry, Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Lucas</hi> of S. Johns neer Colcheſter, Eſq; one of the anceſtors of the Lord Lu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cas.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Cockaine,</hi> Eſq; one of the anceſtors to the now Lord Cockaine.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Mary Harvie,</hi> wife of the late Eliab Harvie, Eſq; and both father and mother of the now Sir Eliab Harvie, Knight-B.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henricus Browne,</hi> a memora<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ble Merchant.</item>
               <item>Dr <hi>Rich. Holdſworth,</hi> Dean of Worceſter, his Tomb re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>built by that great lover of religious and learned men, the honourable Sir Thomas Rich of Berks, Knight and Baronet.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert VVadeſon,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edmond Hammond,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Anne Loker.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Humphry VValcot,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Calvert,</hi> Citizen and Merchant-Taylor.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>VVilliam Chapman,</hi> Citizen and Merchant.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>VVillielmus Philips.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Dagger.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Dr <hi>James Halſey,</hi> Doctor of Divinity.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chriſtopher St. German,</hi> Do<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ctor and Student in Divini<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ty.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>VVilliam Edwards,</hi> ſervant to three memorable Princes, and father of the now Mr Will. Edwards, ſervant like<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>wiſe to Charles 2. the grand Succeſſor of thoſe three Princes.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Anthony Meſſenger.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Barne Roberts,</hi> Eſq; anceſtor to the late Sir William Ro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>berts; and both to the wor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thily honoured Sir William Roberts, very anciently of Wilſden in the County of Middleſex, Baronet, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Taylor,</hi> Eſq; a memora<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ble perſon in his time.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Philippus Paſque,</hi> Eſq; one of the anceſtors of the moſt e<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>minently learned, the late Dr <hi>Paſque.</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="22" facs="tcp:45532:16"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>George Golding,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Anne VVhite.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>George Skevington,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Agnes Dart.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Samuel Alderſey.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Lupſel.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Dimmock,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chriſtian Towerſon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Nicholas Style,</hi> Alderman, of the family of the Styles's in Kent.</item>
               <item>Serjeant-Major <hi>Killigrew.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robertus Jermin de Ruſhbrook</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Offley,</hi> ſon of Hugh Offley, Alderman.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Digges,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Digges,</hi> Eſq; both of the anceſtors of that very ancient and Knightly family of the Digges's in Kent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Conſtantine,</hi> Eſq; ance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtor to William Conſtantine of Dorſet, Eſq; and one of the Benchers of the Middle Temple.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ralph Woodcock,</hi> Alderman of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mary Brigges.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>David Brigges,</hi> Eſq; Sheriff, anceſtor to William Brigges of Rickmerſworth, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gerrard Gore,</hi> Eſq; Alder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Henſhaw,</hi> Eſq; Ca<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ptain, anceſtor to the much accompliſhed Thomas Hen<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſhaw of Kenſington, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas à Kelſy,</hi> anceſtor to the late Colonel Kelſy, ſome<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>times Governour of Dover.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Osbert Moundford,</hi> or <hi>Mount<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fort.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Moundford,</hi> or <hi>Mount<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fort,</hi> anceſtor by the mater<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nal line to Sir John Bramp<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſton, Knight of the Bath; and Sir Mountford Bramp<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſton, one of the Maſters of Chancery.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Franciſca Rudierd,</hi> of that ancient family of the Rudierds in the County of Hants.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mary Collet,</hi> of the family of Sir Henry Collet, Knight.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Francis Waterhouſe,</hi> Eſq; and Bridget his wife; father and mother of the worthily ho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>noured Edward Waterhouſe of Greenford in the County of Middleſex, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mary Waterhouſe,</hi> wife of the laſt Edward Waterhouſe of Greenford in the county of Middleſex, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Hugh Waterhouſe</hi> &amp; <hi>Edward,</hi> their ſons.</item>
               <pb n="23" facs="tcp:45532:16"/>
               <item>Dame <hi>Mary Swift,</hi> wife of Sir Francis Swift of Naſing in the county of Eſſex, Knight; daughter of the above-ſaid Francis Waterhouſe, Eſq; and Bridget his wife.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Dunthorne,</hi> Town-Clerk of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Shelly,</hi> Eſq; one of that honourable family of Sir Charles Shelly in the County of Suſſex.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Lauwrence Gibſon,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Anne Gibſon,</hi> his wife.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Blount,</hi> Citizen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Nicholas Warren,</hi> Gen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Harvie,</hi> Gen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Harvie,</hi> Comptroller of the Cuſtom-houſe.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Burton,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richardus Wilbraham,</hi> Eſq; Common Sergeant of the Citie of London, and ance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtor to that worthy family of the Wilbrahams in Che<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſhire.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Sarich,</hi> Doctor of Divinity.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gulielmus Chriſtmas,</hi> Armig. and Alderman, anceſtor to the worthy William Chriſt<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas Eſq; now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Banniſter,</hi> Eſq; of the late Sir Ed. Banniſters fami<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ly.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Rebecca King,</hi> wife of Mr. <hi>William King,</hi> late Rector of S. Olave Silver-ſtreet, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>CHARLES</hi> the Firſt, of moſt bleſſed memory, his Epi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>taph.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>George Tapsfeild,</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Elliot.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ellinor Clarke.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Randal Pickering.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Slanie,</hi> and</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Humphry Slanie,</hi> their arms in the window of S. Martins Ironmonger-lane.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Rumny,</hi> wife of Sir J. Rumny, Knight.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richardus Chamberlayne, Ge<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>neroſus.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robertus Large, idem.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robertus Cambel,</hi> Eſq; Alder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man, ſon of Sir Thomas, fa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther of the late Sir James Cambel.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Bowyer,</hi> Eſq; Alder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man, very anciently of Kni<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>perſly; anceſtor to Sir Wil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>liam Bowyer of Denham in the County of Buckingham, Knight, and of Sir Edmund Bowyer originally of Suſſex, now of Camberwel in the County of Surrey, Knight-Baronet, and Knight of the Shire.</item>
               <pb n="24" facs="tcp:45532:17"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Morſtead,</hi> Eſq; She<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>riff.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Piot,</hi> Eſq; Alderman, anceſtor to that well-repu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ted family of the Piots in Hertfordſhire.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Guliel. Haliday,</hi> Eſq; Alder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Anne Barker.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Elizabeth Ingram,</hi> wife of Sir Arthur Ingram Knight, and Merchant of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Rowland VVilſon,</hi> Eſq; Al<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>derman.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John VVatts,</hi> Knight, one of the anceſtors of the ho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nourable Sir John Wats in the county of Hertf. Knight and Colonel, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edmund VVhite,</hi> a memorable Citizen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Dalby,</hi> Mercer.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Foxe,</hi> Citizen and Gold<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſmith.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Cecilia Cleyton.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Frances VValler,</hi> daughter of the late Thomas Waller of Beconsfeild, Eſq; and wife of the late Dr. William Boſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>wel, Doctor of Divinity.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Lekimpton,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Herenden,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edmund Herenden,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edmund Herenden,</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Stephen Brackenberry,</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Pemberton,</hi> Gen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Francis Spencer, idem.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Bill,</hi> Armig. father to Sergeant-Major Bill of Cainwood, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gideon de Lawne,</hi> Eſq; ance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtor of the now Sir Gideon de Lawne.</item>
               <item>Dr <hi>VVilliam Gouge,</hi> S.T.D. a moſt memorable Divine, father of Mr Thomas Gouge late Rector of S. Sepulchres, and Dr Gouge, Phyſician.</item>
               <item>Mr <hi>Morehead,</hi> Gen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edmund Symes,</hi> eldeſt ſon of Edmund Symes.</item>
               <item>Col. <hi>Charles Fleetwood</hi>'s La<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dies Funeral-Scutcheons.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Adys,</hi> Goldſmith.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Sutton,</hi> Eſq; Alderman.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Hewit</hi> of London, Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Greenwood,</hi> Painter-Stai<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ner.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Randolph,</hi> Gen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Francis.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Drugo Barantine.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>VVilliam Midgely</hi> of Staple-Inne, Gen. Clerk of the Judgements under the wor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thily honoured <hi>Thomas Ro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>binſon,</hi> Eſq; and chief Pro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thonotary of the Com<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mon
<pb n="25" facs="tcp:45532:17"/> Pleas, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Franck,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Franck,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Nowellus,</hi> Arm. M.D.</item>
               <item>
                  <list>
                     <item>
                        <hi>Jerimoth Drax,</hi>
                     </item>
                     <item>
                        <hi>Joſeph Drax,</hi>
                     </item>
                     <item>
                        <hi>Mary Drax,</hi>
                     </item>
                     <item>
                        <hi>Bamfeild Drax,</hi>
                     </item>
                     <item>
                        <hi>Alexander Drax,</hi>
                     </item>
                  </list> Children of the late old Sir James Drax, Knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mary Drax,</hi> Neece of old Sir James Drax, and wife of Hugh Frankland of Staple-Inne, Gent. of the ancient family of the Franklands of Oldwark in the County of York.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Peter Strelly, Civis &amp; Auri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>faber.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Mary Charleton.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Nicholas Beaumont,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Clapham, Generoſ.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Clapham, filius.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Walterus Haddon,</hi> Maſter of the Requeſts to Qu. Eliz.</item>
               <item>Mr <hi>
                     <gap reason="illegible: omitted in print" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                        <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                     </gap> Waddington,</hi> School<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>maſter of Chriſt-Church.</item>
               <item>Mr. <hi>
                     <gap reason="illegible: omitted in print" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                        <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                     </gap> Haynes,</hi> School-ma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſter of Chriſt-Church.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Rogers,</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ralph Smith.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ludovicus Williams Venedo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cus.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Drew.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gamaliel Pye,</hi> Eſq; anceſtor to the now Sir Edmond Pye, Knight.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Margaret Huſſey.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Dr <hi>Samuel Price,</hi> S.T.D.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Tredway.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Jone Goldſmith.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Radolphus Widdrington.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Anne Phillis Faldo.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Humphry Barret.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Langham,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Marſh.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Dr <hi>William Fuller,</hi> Dean of Durham, and father of the now Lady Jane Walton, wi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dow of the famous Brian Walton, late Biſhop of Che<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſter.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Martha Preſcot,</hi> late wife of Alexander Preſcot, Alder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Browne,</hi> Serjeant-Pain<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ter to Hen. 8. and Alderman of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert South,</hi> Eſq; and Gold<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſmith, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Longstone,</hi> or <hi>Lang<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſton.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Milburne,</hi> Sheriff and Alderman of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Agnes Milburne,</hi> his wife.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Jodosa Frankland,</hi> a good Benefactreſs to Brazen<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>noſe-Colledge,
<pb n="26" facs="tcp:45532:18"/> and a neer ally to Mr Frankland, one of the ſenior Fellows of Brazen-noſe, and late Pro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ctor of the Univerſity of Oxford.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robertus Trappes, Arm.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Burſted.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chriſtopher Waſe,</hi> Goldſmith, one of the anceſtors to that eminently learned Mr Chri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtopher Waſe, S.T.B. and Schoolmaſter of the Free-School of Tunbridge.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Kinnaſton,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Tichbourne,</hi> Eſq; fa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther of the now Robert Tichbourne, late Sheriff, Alderman, and Lord Maior of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Dilkes,</hi> Citizen, and Nephew to William Dilks, ſervant to the Duke of Buc<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kingham.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Battail.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Brett.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Wiat,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richardus Warner.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richardus Coxe.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Dr <hi>John Barwick,</hi> Dean of S. Pauls.</item>
               <item>Dr <hi>Mark Franke,</hi> Archdea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>con of S. Albans.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Petrus Osborne, Armig.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>
                     <gap reason="illegible: omitted in print" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                        <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                     </gap> Berkenhead,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Bedding feild,</hi> Eſq; ſon and heir of Sir Thomas Bed<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dingfeild, Knight.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Arthur Medlycot</hi> of Salop, Eſq; anceſtor to Tho. Med<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lycot of the Middle Tem<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ple, Eſq; and Edmond Med<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lycot of White-hall, his bro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Alicia Primeroſe.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Redman,</hi> Proctor of the Arches.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Arthur Blackmore,</hi> Painter-Stainer, or Arms-Painter, ſon of Capt. Ralph Blackmore Mercer, and ſometimes Pro-Governour of Berwick.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Eliz. Sewil,</hi> wife of Ro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bert Sewil of London, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Col. <hi>Thomas Nevil</hi> his Lady, and other neer relations.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Peter Bradſhaw,</hi> Eſq; anceſtor to Mr Francis Bradſhaw, late Draper of London, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Guliel. Huſe, Armig.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Antonius Huſe, Armig.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Florence Caldwel,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Eliz. Mennel,</hi> of that ancient family of the Mennels in the County of Derby, daughter of Mr Menel, and neece of Alderman Mennel, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Cook.</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="27" facs="tcp:45532:18"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Yeardly.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Jaſper Cholmely.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Antrobus.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Amy Adlyn,</hi> or <hi>Edlyn.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Dr <hi>Gouldſton de Wymond<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ham,</hi> M.D. a memorable Phyſician.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Ley,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Barnard.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Helias Jones.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Hen. Long,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Nicholſon,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Dom. de Hatfeild.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Maria Martin.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Anthony Jocelyn,</hi> Eſq; and</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chriſtopher Marſh,</hi> Eſq; both menial ſervants to the Right honourable the Lady Dow<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ager of Dorſet and Pem<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>broke.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>David Smith,</hi> Eſq; Embroy<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>derer to Qu. Eliz.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Smith,</hi> Eſq; Alder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man, his ſon.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Auſtin,</hi> Eſq; anceſtor to William Auſtin, formerly of Lincolns Inne, Eſq; and both anceſtors to Sir James Auſtin of the County of Surrey, Knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ignatius Jones,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Askough,</hi> Citizen and Grocer, husband to Mris A<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lice Askough now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Norgate,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ellis Hilton,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Mr <hi>Sampſon,</hi> Embroyderer.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Parce,</hi> Gen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Griffith Lloyd,</hi> Doctor of the Civil Law.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Philipot,</hi> Eſq; Somerſet-Herald, and father of that learned Antiquary, Scholar and Herald, Tho. Philipot Eſq;. now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Clivelod.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ellis Criſpe,</hi> wife of the late Ellis Criſpe, Alderman; fa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther and mother to the ho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nourable Sir Nich. Chiſpe deceaſed.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Roger Ford.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Ireland,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Stock,</hi> a moſt me<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>morable Divine, and long Rector of Alhallows Bread<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Robſon,</hi> Salter, a worthy Benefactor to the Poor.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Suckly;</hi> Eſq; Sheriff of London; anceſtor of Ralph Suckly Eſq; one of the Pro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ctors of the high Court of Admiralty.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Albany,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Beaumond,</hi> or <hi>Bean<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mont.</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="28" facs="tcp:45532:19"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Melliſh.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Hulſton.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Dunſtarre.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Lieutenant-Colonel <hi>John Lane</hi> Armig. father of John Lane whole-ſale-Grocer.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Leonard Smith.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Dorothy Harby.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Sandhill.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Haſlefoot,</hi> Vintner.</item>
               <item>Mr. <hi>Capwood.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mr. <hi>Moſely.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Bowes.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Wellens.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richardus Sturges.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Blitheman.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Alderman <hi>Lewen.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Agnes Lewen,</hi> his wife.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Burton.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Walter Timberlack.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth Timberlack.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth Acton.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Chichely,</hi> Eſq; one of the anceſtors of the worthily honoured Henry Chichely, Eſq; <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Randal.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Anthony Cage.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gaius Newman,</hi> father of <gap reason="illegible: omitted in print" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Anne Middleton.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Pert.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Metcalf Allington.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Dane,</hi> Alderman and Sheriff, anceſtor to <gap reason="illegible: omitted in print" resp="#OXF" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Alice Daniel.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Harper.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Robinſon,</hi> of the county of Glouceſter, Eſq; father-in-law to the Lady Mico now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Beſwick,</hi> Alderman.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Poultney,</hi> Eſq; She<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>riff, Alderman, and one of the founders of S. Lawrence Poultney's Church.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Heſter Mountney.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Daniel Harvie</hi> of Folkſton in the county of Kent, Eſq; father of the honourable Sir Daniel Harvie of Surry, Knight and Baronet, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Nelſon,</hi> ſon of John Nelſon, Merchant.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Cromer.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Coſyn,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Wilburgis Gretſyin.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>R. Moore,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Franck,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Shaw,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert VVithins,</hi> Armig. Al<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>derman and Sheriff.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Francis VVithins,</hi> Eſq; his ſon.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Gurney,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>VVilielmus Litchfeild.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Brickles.</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="29" facs="tcp:45532:19"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Francis Goldſmith.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Chamberlayne.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Humphry Clark,</hi> Eſq; Depu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ty of Alhallows Ward, and father of Humphry Clark of the M. Temple.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Coulſon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Deputy <hi>Green.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Dr. <hi>Reginald VVest,</hi> S.T.D.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Gelſon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Holt,</hi> Eſq; Alderman of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Alexander Holt,</hi> Eſq; Alder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man of London; both of them very anciently of that memorable family of the Holts of Grizlehurſt in the county of Lancaſter; and both anceſtors to Alexander Holt, Eſq; and Alderman, yet living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Glover.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Cambden,</hi> Gen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Eliz. Freeman.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Cheſlyn,</hi> Alderman.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Cheſlyn,</hi> a Divine, his ſon.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes à Moore.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Jane Abraham.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Anna Saris.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Theophilus Biddolph,</hi> ſon of Sir Theophilus Biddolph Knight and Baronet.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Rainwel.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Rainwel.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Chatterton,</hi> wife of Mr. Chatterton of Pater-noſter<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>row.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>George Clint.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Antonius Abdy,</hi> Armig ance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtor to Sir Robert Abdy, and Sir Thomas Abdy, both of Eſſex, Knights Ba.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Humphry Turner.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Margaret Turner.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Nicholas de Na le.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Stow,</hi> the Cities Chrono<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>loger.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Symon Burton.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Alice Coldock,</hi> or <hi>Bing.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Hills.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Dr <hi>Henry Man,</hi> Doctor of Di<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vinity.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Joane Cartwright.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Dorothy Greſwold.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Warner,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Philip Malpas</hi> Eſq;. Sheriff of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Hugh Offley,</hi> Eſq; and Sheriff.</item>
               <item>Mr. <hi>John Smith.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Tovie.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Bartholomew Ettenor.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Viner,</hi> Eſq; ſon of the late Sir Thomas, and bro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther of Sir George Viner, Knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Frances Cook,</hi> wife of Pau<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lus Ambroſius Cook.</item>
               <pb facs="tcp:45532:20"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Roger Marſhal,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Alice Gilbourne.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chriſtophorus Newman.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Jackman,</hi> Eſq; She<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>riff of London.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Eliz. Ingram,</hi> wife of Sir Arthur Ingram, Knight, and Merchant of London.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Anne Horton,</hi> wife of Mr Thomas Horton.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Gunſton,</hi> ſiſter of Serje<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ant-Major Gunſton.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Middleton,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Bateman</hi> Eſq; Cham<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>berlain of London, and an<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ceſtor to Richard Bateman, Eſq; Sir Anthony, Sir Willi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>am Bateman, Knights; and Sir Thomas Bateman, Baro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>net; all four brothers.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Bernard Hide</hi> of Boreplace in the county of Kent, Eſq; anceſtor to the worthily ho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>noured Sir <hi>Bernard Hide</hi> of Kent, Knight-B.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Heſter Hide,</hi> wife of the ſaid Bernard.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Yong,</hi> Eſq; an eminent Eaſtland Merchant.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Keyte,</hi> Armig. anceſtor to the worthily honoured Sir Jonathan Keyte of the County of Hertf. Knight-B.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Hewit,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Mr. <hi>Woodroffe,</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Ruſſel,</hi> Eſq; husband of the Lady Waterman, now wife of Sir George Water<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man, Knight-B.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Heardſman,</hi> Alderman.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Bacon,</hi> Alderman.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Samuel Reynolds.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Sarah Forth,</hi> wife of the worthy Mr. Hugh Forth, Merchant, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Margaret Bayly,</hi> or <hi>Reynolds.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Wyche.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Page,</hi> Apothecary, a perſon very memorable.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Hackney,</hi> Sheriff.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert VVood,</hi> Eſq; Deputy of Billings-gate Ward, fa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther of William Wood, Eſq; now living.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Alicia Farwel,</hi> wife of Philip Farwel.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Bewly,</hi> wife of Thomas Bewly of Hall-place in the county of Kent, Gent.</item>
               <item>Mr <hi>Thomas Bewly,</hi> late of Grays Inne, their ſon.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Em. Charleton.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Munne,</hi> Merchant.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chriſtopher Holt,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Chamberlayne,</hi> M.D.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mary Moſſe.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Element,</hi> Merchant-tay<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lor.</item>
               <pb facs="tcp:45532:20"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Sarah Manning.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Eliz. Clarke,</hi> wife of Henry Clark, Draper.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Brian Vere.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Web,</hi> Eſq; Gentleman<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>uſher to H. 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Lucius Lucas,</hi> an eminent Mer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chant.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robertus Thacker.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Jonas à Weely</hi> of Amſterdam.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Charity Cotton,</hi> wife of Geo. Cotton, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Barnes,</hi> a great Benefa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ctreſs.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Georgius Chriſtophorus Oſter<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>hauſen.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Iſaacſon,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Derham,</hi> ſon of Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas Derham of Derham-Grange.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Jane Hartly.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Greenſmith.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Capt. <hi>James Birkdel.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>George Smithes.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Lionel Mellington,</hi> ſon of Sir Robert Mellington.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Tho. Curteſius,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Emanuel de Meteren.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Katherine Woodward,</hi> wi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dow.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Hewit.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Ingram.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Dr <hi>Peter Turner,</hi> M.D.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Stoddard,</hi> Eſq; ance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtor of George Stoddard, Eſq; father of the late Sir Nicholas Stoddard of Kent, Knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Philippus Wylander.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Highlord,</hi> Eſq; Alder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Beckenham,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ferdinando Alvarez, Merca<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tor eminens.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>George Watts.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Tho. Burnel.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Cely.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Goure,</hi> Prince of Po<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ets in his time, and anceſtor to that moſt ancient and e<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>minent family of the Goures of Stitinham in the county of York.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Mourton.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Auſtin,</hi> Eſq; father of Sir James Auſtin of Sur<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rey, Knight; and William Auſtin of Grays Inne, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Peter Humble,</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Tho. Cure,</hi> Eſq; Great grand<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>father to A. Cure of the In<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ner Temple, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Bingham,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Symons,</hi> Citizen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Trehearne,</hi> Gentleman<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>porter to King James.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Margaret Maynard.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mary Fiſher,</hi> wife of Payne
<pb facs="tcp:45532:21"/> Fiſher, and daughter of Sir Tho. Neale, and the Lady Eliz. Freke; mother of Ma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>jor Payne Fiſher now living, Author of this Collection.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richardus Benefield,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Emmerſon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Samuel Popular.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Anne Warcup.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mary Bareford,</hi> with ſeveral children of Mr Jonathan Bareford.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Dorothea Howard.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mark Proudfoot.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Wood.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Jeremy Smith.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Gawen.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Samuel Winne.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Cooke.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Hayman.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Joſeph Collier.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>George Buggins.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Chilcot.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Garrard.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Sturton,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Ward.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Drawer.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edw. Ball.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Benſon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Malledge.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Thomas.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Eſton,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Fairford.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Philip.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Nichols.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Barbara Thomaſin.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Capt. <hi>Thomas Sparling.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Col. <hi>Thomſon</hi>'s Ladies Eſcut<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cheon.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>George Rooks.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Matthew Clark.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Evans.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Savage.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Jones,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Hobſon,</hi> ſon of Do<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ctor William Hobſon.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Suſanna Jones.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Francis Rudierd.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Margaret Derham.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth Boyd.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Aldridge.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Captain <hi>Randal Moulton,</hi> husband of Rebecca Moul<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ton, third ſon of the famous Captain Robert Moulton, Sometimes Vice-Admiral of England, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> and younger brother of the yet-living and valiant Captain Robert Moulton, now in his Maje<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſties ſervice.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Auſten,</hi> Eſq; a memo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rable Citizen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Auſten,</hi> Eſq;</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Auſten,</hi> Eſq; his ſons; two hopeful Gentlemen, lately of Lincolns Inne.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Jane Hanſly.</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="33" facs="tcp:45532:21"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Georgius Gippe,</hi> Eſq; one of the Judges in the Sheriffs Court.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Seymour,</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Humphry Starky,</hi> Knight, Lord Chief Baron of the Exchequer.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Rivet Eldred,</hi> Knight, a memorable Merchant, and husband of that nobly ver<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tuous Dame Anne Eldred, daughter of Mr John Black<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>wel of Hornidge in the county of Salop</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Cavendiſh,</hi> Eſq; one of the anceſtors of the Illu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtrious William Cavendiſh, Duke, Marquis, and Earl of Newcaſtle.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Richard Fen,</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, Grandfather to the worthy Richard Fen of Hall<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>place (in Hurly-pariſh) in the county of Berks, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Richard Gurney,</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, whoſe two daughters (Co-heirs) were married to the Right Hono<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rable the Lord Richardſon, and Sir John Pettus, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Bayly,</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Stephen Peacock,</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, anceſtor to the Knightly family of the Pea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cocks in Middleſex, where<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>of Richard Peacock of that delicate ſeat of Finchly, Eſq; is preſent proprietor.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Anne Leighe.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Katharine Lively.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Theodoſia Vaveſour.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mr <hi>John Weaver,</hi> that writ the Acts and Monuments.</item>
               <item>Mr Juſtice <hi>Long.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Knightly,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Frances White.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Anne Blount.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Dalliſon,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Mr <hi>Edward Vaughan.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Rogerus Wood,</hi> Sergeant at Arms.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Francis Butler.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Palmer</hi> of Clerkenwel, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Dudly Palmer</hi> of Grays Inne, Eſq; his Grandchilde.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth Crofts.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Wandesford</hi> of Pick<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>hill in the county of York, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Cropley,</hi> Eſq; ſon of the honourable Sir John Cropley, Knight-Baronet.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Jorden Briſet,</hi> Founder of Clerkenwel-Priory.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth Trotman,</hi> wife of
<pb n="34" facs="tcp:45532:22"/> Samuel Trotman of the Inner Temple, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Vaughan,</hi> Maſter of Arts, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Sutton,</hi> Eſq; Founder of that famous Society of the Charter-houſe.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Lawes,</hi> Eſq; Executor of Thomas Sutton.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Francis Beaumont,</hi> Eſq; ſome<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>times Governour of the Charter-houſe.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Bunce,</hi> Eſq; father of the honourable Sir James Bunce, Knight and Baronet, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Raynie,</hi> Eſq; anceſtor of the now Sir John Raynie of Wrothan in the County of Kent, Baronet.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Denne,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Jane Adams,</hi> wife of Thomas Adams of Bater<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſea, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ambroſe Jennings,</hi> Ironmon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ger.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes de Coggeſhal,</hi> a moſt famous Citizen.</item>
               <item>Mr <hi>Sybals,</hi> ſon of the learn<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ed and much-obliging Dr Sybals, D.D. late of Cler<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kenwel.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Dogget,</hi> Sheriff.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chriſtophorus Southouſe, Re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gistarrius Curiae Cant.</hi> ance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtor to the Southouſes of Kent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>rſula Beſiney,</hi> daughter of Nicholas Beſtney, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Weldon,</hi> ſecond ſon of Ralph Weldon of Swanſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>comb in Kent, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Eliz. Faſſelts,</hi> widow.</item>
               <item>Mr. <hi>Lamb,</hi> founder of S. James Chappel in the Wall, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Glover,</hi> Armig. So<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>merſet-Herald, Grandfather by the mothers ſide to Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas Philipot of Southend in Kent, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Busby,</hi> Citizen, and a good Benefactor.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>George Chute,</hi> Eſq; Standard<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bearer to H. 8. at Bulloigne, and anceſtor to that Knight<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ly family of the Chutes in Kent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Roper.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Harvist,</hi> Gen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Charles Langley,</hi> idem.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Matthew Palmer</hi> ſenior, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Matthew Palmer,</hi> his Grand<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>childe, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Sarah Gooderick,</hi> daughter to Sir William Bodenham, Knight.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Conſtance Whitney,</hi> daughter of Sir Robert Whitney of
<pb n="35" facs="tcp:45532:22"/> Whitney in the county of Hertford, Knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Fox, Martyrologus Anglicanus.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Weſterne.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Katherine Bennet.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Captain <hi>Biller</hi>'s two daugh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ters.</item>
               <item>Colonel <hi>John Dove,</hi> father of John Dove of Sarum, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Bullen,</hi> or <hi>Bollen.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Gifford,</hi> Gen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Crowly,</hi> Vicar of Crip<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ple-gate.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Speed,</hi> Chronologer, Grandfather of Mr Samuel Speed of Fleetſtreet, Book<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſeller.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Suſanna Speed,</hi> wife of the ſaid John Speed.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Stapley,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Eliz. Smith,</hi> wife of that religious and learned man, and lover of religious and learned men, Mr Richard Smith of Moor-fields, Gen. and ſometimes Secondary of the Poultry-Counter.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Hawly,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>Mr <hi>Hen. Colbron.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robertus Cage,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Roſe Hitchings.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Jane Smith,</hi> wife of John Smith of Bunhill, Eſq; <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <list>
                     <item>Mris <hi>Ellen Monyns,</hi>
                     </item>
                     <item>Mris <hi>Frances Monyns;</hi>
                     </item>
                  </list> Daughters of Sir William Monyns of Kent, Baronet.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Ravenſcroft,</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Margaret Lucie,</hi> daughter of Sir Thomas Lucie of Charle<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cot, Knight.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Elizabeth Aſhton.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Glasbrook,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Anne Branch.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Downes.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Buckley.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Milſon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Margaret Litchervet.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Purde.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Peter Swift.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Cotton,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Southerton,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Gillet,</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Francis Smith.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Jane Duck,</hi> daughter of the late Dr Duck.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Maria Wotton,</hi> of the noble family of the Wottons of Kent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Guil. Mill,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Mill, filius.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Pearce Edgecombe</hi> of Mount-Edgecombe, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Michael Crud, Theologus.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Elizabeth Westfeild,</hi> wife of Dr Thomas Weſt<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>feild, Biſhop of Briſtol.</item>
               <pb n="36" facs="tcp:45532:23"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Barbara Bradberry.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chriſtophorus Tameworth,</hi> Eſq;</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Percival Smalpace,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Morley,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth VVotton.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Francis Southerton.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Goodwine.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Greek.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Neale,</hi> ſon of Sir Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas Neale, Knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Suſanna Lyon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Judith Plat,</hi> daughter of Sir Hugh Plat, Knight.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Sparrow,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Sarah Stirrop,</hi> wife of Nathaniel Stirrop, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Clement Scudamour,</hi> Kt. Lord Maior; a branch of that flouriſhing and noble family of the Scudamours in the County of Here<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ford.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Kinnon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Stephens.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Serjeant-Major <hi>Alſop.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Trevor,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Randolph Trevor,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>R. Truſſel,</hi> Gent. one of the anceſtors of the honourable Colonel Truſſel, ſometimes of Pater-noſter-row.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Alington,</hi> Eſq; Ma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſter of the Rolls.</item>
               <item>Dr <hi>John Yong,</hi> Dean of York, Maſter of the Rolls.</item>
               <item>Dom. <hi>Rahere,</hi> firſt founder and Prior of great S. Bartholo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mews.</item>
               <item>Captain <hi>John Millet,</hi> Mari<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ner.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Antonius Lowe,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Eilis Yong,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Cooke,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Percilanus Smalpace,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>Dr <hi>Francis Antony,</hi> M.D.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Eliz. Freſhwale.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Orme.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Nicholas Orme.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Abigal Colt.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Mary Pit.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Rivers,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>VVilliam Boulton,</hi> the laſt Pri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>or of great S. Bartholo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mews.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Guil. Hone.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>VVilliam Baker.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Balthorp,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Shirly,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Petrus Toutevile,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Anne VVeſtwick.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Francis Eagles field.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richardus Ley.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Dury.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>VValter Inſham.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ellinor Inſham.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Shipley.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Pindar.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mary Peiſly.</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="37" facs="tcp:45532:23"/>
               <item>Sir <hi>Robert Peake,</hi> Knight and Colonel, ſometimes Gover<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nour of Baſing-houſe, buried lately in S. Sepulchres, conti<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>guous to, or elſe in the ſelf<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſame grave of</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Jaſper Churchill,</hi> Gent. de<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſcended from that ancient family of the Churchills in the Weſt, and father of the worthily honoured John Churchill of Churchill, Eſq; one of the Seniors of Lin<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>colns Inne; and alſo of Mr Jaſper Churchill, Gold<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſmith, with his brother Thomas.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Frampton,</hi> Eſq; of that ancient family of the Fram<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ptons of Upway in the county of Dorſet; and an<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ceſtor to Mr John Fram<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>pton of S. Martins lane in the fields.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Sturgeon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Marks.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Randal,</hi> City-Plum<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mer.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Samuel Cartwright.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Guil. Freſhwater.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Lawrence Dalton,</hi> Eſq; <hi>Ju<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>riſconſultus.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Cutbert Fetherſton,</hi> one of the anceſtors of the worthily honoured Sir Heneage Fe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>therſton, Baronet, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Nicholas Hare,</hi> Eſq; original<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ly from France, brother to the Right Honourable <hi>Hugh Hare,</hi> Baron of Colerain, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Brook,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Roſamond Nevil.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Lingham,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richardus Mardon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Laurentius Bartlet.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Guil. Morecroft,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Horſpool.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Pope</hi> of Cliffords Inne.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gerrard Leigh,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Roſamond Wright.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Crouch.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Cordwel.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Valence,</hi> Eſq; J.C. of Lincolns Inne.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Stephen Poule,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Whitchcot,</hi> Eſq; ſon of Thomas Whitchcot, Eſq; both anceſtors to the hono<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rable Sir Jerom Whitchcot, Knight-B. and Colonel, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> and alſo of the moſt learned Dr Whitchcot, late of Cam<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bridge.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Mary Preſcot.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Daugges,</hi> ſon of Wil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>liam Daugges of Newgat<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtreet
<pb n="38" facs="tcp:45532:24"/> in the county of Hert<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ford, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mary Barker.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Dacres,</hi> Eſq; anceſtor to the worthily honoured Sir Thomas Dacres of Cheſten<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ham in the county of Hert<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ford, Knight, of a very an<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cient ſtanding.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth North, Generoſa.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Reginald Green,</hi> Gen.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Mary Davis.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Guil. Chapman.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>David Daviſon,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth Daviſon,</hi> daughter of Thomas Founes of Ply<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mouth, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Alexander Eaton.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Valentine Elſing.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Pope,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henricus Bernard inter. Temp. Armig.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Katherine Jones,</hi> daughter of Rowland Morgan.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Gate, unus Baronum Scaccarii.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John White,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Charles Potts,</hi> Eſq; one of the Benchers of the Middle Temple.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Goldsborough,</hi> of the Middle Temple, Armig. one of the Prothonotaries of the Common Pleas.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edmond Plowden,</hi> Eſq; <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Roope,</hi> ſon of John Roope of Dartmouth, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gregory Cole,</hi> of Buckiſh in the county of Devon, Ar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Tobias Newcourt,</hi> of Pickwel in the county of Devon, Ar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Heyhoe,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Marſton Weely.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ed. Turnor,</hi> of Parrington in the county of Eſſex, Eſq;. father of the honourable Sir Edward Turnor, Knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> and Arthur Turnor, Serjeant at Law, ſecond ſon of the ſaid Edmund, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Daniel Cudmore</hi> of Loxborne in the county of Devon, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes de la Bearne, Med. Temp. Socius.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Norden int. Templ.</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henricus Beaumont, int. Temp. Armig.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Osborne,</hi> Eſq; <hi>int. Temp.</hi> J.C.</item>
               <item>Dom. <hi>Richardus Lempſter, Capellanus.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>David Guinne</hi> of the county of Brecknock, Eſq;.</item>
               <pb n="39" facs="tcp:45532:24"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Charton</hi> of Wolvering<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ton in the county of Salop, Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Clement Coke</hi> of Langford in the county of Derby, Ar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John French</hi> Eſq; Bencher of the Inner Temple.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Williams, Venedocus,</hi> Gen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Charles Heath,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Rudolphus Quarterman,</hi> Gen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Naſh,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Denne,</hi> very anciently of Kent, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Portman,</hi> Eſq; one of the Benchers of the Tem<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ple, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Daniel Liſle,</hi> Eſq; one of the younger ſons of Sir William Liſle, Knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Dom. Martinus, Juriſconſul<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tus eminens.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Littleton,</hi> Eſq; ſon of Sir Thomas Littleton, Knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Selden,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Rowlandus Jewks,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edvardus Vaughan,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Rogerus Biſhop,</hi> Gen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edvardus Hide,</hi> Eſq; ſon of the Right Honourable Ed<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ward Earl of Clarendon, and Lord Chancellor of England, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Guil. Langſton de</hi> Hanly-Ca<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtle.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mark Blackmoore,</hi> J.C.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edvardus Bernard,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Margaret Hutchinſon,</hi> wife of Ralph Hutchinſon.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Katharine Beaumont.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Nathaniel Stirrop,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Lambert,</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Bradley,</hi> Citizen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Burnefold,</hi> Citizen, with his wife.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Suſanna Treſwel,</hi> wife of Ro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bert Treſwel, Purſuivant at Arms.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Bartholomew Read,</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Williamſon,</hi> of great Markham in the coun<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ty of Nottingham, Knight and Baronet.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Elizabeth Puckering,</hi> wife of Sir Thomas Pucke<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ring, Knight and Baronet.</item>
               <item>The Lord <hi>William Fitz-War<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ren,</hi> and <hi>Iſabel</hi> his wife, ſometimes Queen of the Iſle of Man.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Dominicus ab Heila, Nobilis.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Roberts,</hi> a memorable Citizen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Thorne,</hi> an eminent Benefactor.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Beecher,</hi> Eſq; Sheriff
<pb n="40" facs="tcp:45532:25"/> and Alderman, the improver of that worthy family of the Becchers in the county of Bedford.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Adam Bamme,</hi> Maior of Lon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>don, 1397.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Bamme,</hi> his ſon, of Gilingham in the County of Kent, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Walton,</hi> Gent. buried <hi>anno Dom.</hi> 1401.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Combes,</hi> Stockfiſh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>monger, Sheriff of London 1452 a great Benefactor to his Pariſh-Church.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Dryland,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Yevele,</hi> Free-Maſon to Edw. 3. <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Long</hi> of Bedford-ſhire, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Jawdrell,</hi> Merchant-Taylor.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Olney,</hi> Knight, Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Young,</hi> Knight, and Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Ruſſel,</hi> Eſq; Sollici<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tor-General to Queen Eli<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>zabeth.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>George Holman,</hi> Gent. Ance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtor to the Knightly family of the Holmans in the coun<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ty of Northampton.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Ralph Freeman,</hi> Knight, Lord Maior, a moſt memo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rable perſon, and Uncle to the worthily honored Ralph Freeman in the County of Herts, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Lowe,</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Murrell,</hi> Grocer, and <hi>Martha Murrell.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Colonel <hi>Barriff,</hi> his Enſignes hanging over him.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Matchell,</hi> Eſq; and Al<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>derman of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Cantelaw,</hi> Mercer, and Merchant of the Staple of Calice.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Champion,</hi> Citizen and Grocer.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Browne,</hi> ſon of Hum<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>phry Browne, Merchant.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Simon Betach,</hi> ſon of Robert Betach, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Simon Edmonds,</hi> Eſq; Alder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man, Sheriff, and Lo. Maior elect of London; one of the anceſtors of the worthy family of Edmonds of Kings Langley in the county of Herts, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Hugh Wyche,</hi> Knight, Lo. Maior, one of the anceſtors of the much honoured Sir Cyril Wyche, and Sir Peter Wyche, both brothers, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="41" facs="tcp:45532:25"/>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Leighe,</hi> Knight buried in the Church of S. Leonard Shoreditch.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Ralph Warren,</hi> Knight Alderman, and twice Lord Maior.</item>
               <item>Dr <hi>Mark Frank,</hi> S.T.D. and Archdeacon of S. Albans.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>J. Pennyfather,</hi> Eſq; having fined for Sheriff and Alder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert South,</hi> Eſq; Citizen and Goldſmith of London.</item>
               <item>The Lady <hi>Gurney,</hi> wife of the ſaid Robert South, and Grandmother of Madam Mary Montague, wife of the honourable Mr Montague the Queens Attorney, and daughter of Sir John Aube<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ry of Wales.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Margaret Withy,</hi> late wife of Mr. John Withy, Gent. and Painter-Stainer of London.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Alice Talbot,</hi> late wife of Thomas Talbot of Great-Ealing in the county of Middleſex, Eſq; and ſome<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>times Captain of Foot; ve<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ry anciently of Yorkſhire.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Saye,</hi> ſon of William Saye, Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Hele,</hi> Eſq; ſon and heir of Sir John Hele of Wen<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bury, Knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Aldworth,</hi> Eſq; with Elizabeth his wife.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Radulphus Rookeby,</hi> Hoſp. Lincoln. J.C.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gulielmus Horſnel,</hi> Gen. very anciently of Horſnel-crouch (or Horſnel-croſs) in Kent, and father of John and George Horſnel, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Evering</hi> of Grays Inne, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Frances Beverſham,</hi> wife of William Beverſham of Grays Inne, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Sarah Jay,</hi> onely daugh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ter of Mr George Jay, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Ellinour Tilus,</hi> ſecond wife of Mr Silias Titus, fa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther of Silias Titus of his Majeſties Bed-chamber, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Sayer,</hi> Stationer.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Gerrard,</hi> ſon of Phi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lip Gerrard of Grays Inne, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Gerrard,</hi> late of Grays Inne, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth Ade,</hi> wife of John Ade.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Elizabeth Bretton,</hi> &amp;c. <hi>Chriſtopher Sherland,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Dr <hi>Raphiel Throckmorton,</hi> S.T.D. Archdeacon of Line.</item>
               <pb n="42" facs="tcp:45532:26"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Clement Plannard.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>R. Marſton,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Thorney,</hi> a memorable Chirurgeon.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Heneage,</hi> Eſq; ſon of Sir Tho. Heneage, Knight.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Ellinor Harecourt,</hi> wife of George Harecourt, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Matthew Bull.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Mallory.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Roger Carlile.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Eliz. Biſpham,</hi> late wife of Dr William Biſpham, Pre<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bend of Weſtcheſter.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Eliz. Hodges.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Philippus Kempe.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Reginaldus Biens,</hi> Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ruth Rhetorick.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Roger Williams</hi> of Grays Inn, Armig.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Stapylton de Wighill com. Ebor.</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Margaret Ludlowe.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edwardus Scarisbrick, Ar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mig.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Collet.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Matthaeus Bust.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Tipper,</hi> Eſquire of the body to the late King James.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Michael Lewis de Colyweſton,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Jo. Topham.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Marles.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Bennet,</hi> Eſq; ſon and heir of Sir Robert Bennet of Broadwinſor, Knight.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Matthias St. George,</hi> daugh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ter of of Sir Richard St. George Knight.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Rob. Cooke de Mileham comit. Norf.</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Worſely</hi> of the Iſle of Wight, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Katharine Eyre.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Wyburne,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Jane Carpenter.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Eliz. Wall,</hi> wife of John Wall.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Tho. Vavaſour,</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth Acton,</hi> daughter of Hen. Acton.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Walter Timberlack.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Anne Peers,</hi> wife of Ed<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mond Peers, very anciently of Shropſhire, late Citizen and Grocer of London.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Kobert Houghton,</hi> Knight, one of the Juſtices of the Common Pleas.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Margaret Talbot.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Anne Horton,</hi> wife of <hi>Thomas Horton.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Henry Calthorp,</hi> Knight, deſcended from Sir Henry Calthorp, Knight, <hi>temp. Hen.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Roger Drake,</hi> Eſq; father of Dr Drake, S.T.D. and Cha<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>plain
<pb n="43" facs="tcp:45532:26"/> in Ordinary to his Ma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>jeſtie; and of Dr Roger Drake, M.D. his brother.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>George Miller</hi> of London, Gen. and Printer, father to Simon Miller of St Pauls Churchyard, Bookſeller.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edmund Symes,</hi> eldeſt ſon of Edmund Symes.</item>
               <item>Mr <hi>Morehead.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Mr <hi>Evans.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Dr <hi>William Gouge,</hi> Doctor of Divinity, and father of Mr. Thomas Gouge many years of St Sepulchres, and of Dr Gouge the Phyſician his brother.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Nicholas Kempe,</hi> Knight, one of the High-Commiſſi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>on-Court.</item>
               <item>The Lady <hi>Sarah Kempe.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Fowler,</hi> Eſq; father of Sir Thomas Fowler, Knight-Baronet.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Anne Chetwind,</hi> wife of Hen<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ry Chetwind, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henricus Grimſton,</hi> Eſq; third ſon of the honourable Sir Harbottle Grimſton of the county of Eſſex, Baronet, and Maſter of the Rolls, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gabriel Pannel</hi> of London, Leatherſeller.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Markham,</hi> Eſq; Serjeaht at Arms to King James.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Hugo, Daſh field,</hi> ſervant to the late Lord Coventry.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edmuad Pott</hi> of Pott in the County of Cheſter, Gent.</item>
               <item>Dr <hi>William Langham,</hi> one of the Prebends of Lichfield, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Fyboll,</hi> Eſq; ſon and heir of Sir William Fyboll of Woodland in the county of Dorſet, Knight.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henricus Wilks, Rector Eccle<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſiae Sancti Nicolai Olave.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Hill,</hi> Eſq; Maſter of the Wine-cellar to King H. 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ellinor,</hi> daughter of <hi>J. Wilkes</hi> of Michel-Grove in the county of Suſſex, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Richard Merlow,</hi> Lord Maior of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Porter,</hi> Eſq; Clerk of the Crown.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Alexander Carlile,</hi> Vintner.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Rayning, Gen.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Agnes Chenie,</hi> wife of Willi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>am Chenie, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Glanvile, Armig.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Bayly,</hi> Knight, and Lord Maior of Lon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>don.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Woodfald,</hi> Eſq; Al<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>derman of London.</item>
               <pb n="44" facs="tcp:45532:27"/>
               <item>Mr <hi>Stockton,</hi> Fiſhmonger, a memorable Citizen.</item>
               <item>Mris <hi>Joane Coppinger,</hi> widow of William Coppinger, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Paynard,</hi> alias <hi>Thomas Aylwood,</hi> Secretary to the Lord Cromwel, Chancellor of England, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Johannes Ingram, Civis &amp; Piſcenarius.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Roger Huming,</hi> Fiſhmonger, and Purveyor to King H. 8. <hi>Tho Nichols,</hi> Citizen and Fiſh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>monger.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Nicholaus Wolbergh, Civis &amp; Piſcenarius.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Orenge,</hi> Gent. with <hi>A<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gnes</hi> his wife.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Guil. Elgaſton, Civis &amp; Piſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cenarius.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Guil. Coggeſhal, Civis &amp; Piſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cenarius.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Fearnefold,</hi> Citizen and Fiſhmonger.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Paddington,</hi> Citizen and Fiſhmonger.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Story,</hi> Citizen and Fiſhmonger.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Warner,</hi> Eſq; ſon of Sir Ed. Warner, Knight.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Warner,</hi> Eſq; ſon of Sir Ed. Warner, Knight.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Gerbridge,</hi> Mercer, and Merchant adventurer.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Muſchamp,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Gulielmus Morecroft, Armig.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Brewſter,</hi> Eſq; one of the anceſtors to John Brew<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſter of Grays Inne, Eſq; and alſo of Mr Edward Brew<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſter of St Pauls Churchyard, Citizen and Book ſeller.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Anne Barret,</hi> wife of Henry Barret; with ten of her children.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Suſanna King,</hi> wife of Da<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>niel King.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Chriſtmas,</hi> Stone-cutter, and Common-council-man.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Reave,</hi> Citizen and Wax-chandler.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth,</hi> wife of Tho. Bil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lingſly, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Tickhill,</hi> Gent. and <hi>Philip</hi> his wife.</item>
               <item>Mr <hi>John Giffard,</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Brocas,</hi> Gent. ſervant to the late Earl of Surrey.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Francis Barrantine de Haſely Com. Oxf.</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Arthur Dacres,</hi> ſon and heir of the late Lord Dacres.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Blundel,</hi> Citizen and Fruiterer of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Ravening,</hi> Citizen and Salter.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>VVilliam Claytwel,</hi> Citizen and Fruiterer.</item>
               <pb n="45" facs="tcp:45532:27"/>
               <item>Sir <hi>Henry Collet,</hi> Knight, twice Lord Maior of London.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Philip Boyl,</hi> a valiant Knight of Arragon, whoſe Anceſtors were Founders of Abby, or Abbats Boyl in Ireland; which Sir <hi>Philip</hi> was one of the ancient Pro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>genitors of the Right Ho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nourable Richard Boyl, Earl of Burlington, and Earl Corck; and of his two noble Brothers, the right honoura<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ble Roger Earl of Orery, and the right honourable Robert Boyl, his younger Brother, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Dawtry,</hi> of Lincolns Inn, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Deborah Gerbier,</hi> wife of Sir Balthazar Gerbier Knight.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth Warcop,</hi> (or War cup) eldeſt Daughter of Ro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dolph Warcup of Engliſh, in the County of Oxford, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Captain <hi>William Buſhel.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Bobert Clark,</hi> Eſq; ſon of Ro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ger Clark, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Jane Nevel,</hi> alias <hi>Jane Det<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nick.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Jane Husbands,</hi> wife to Cap<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tain William Husbands.</item>
               <item>Col. <hi>Humphry Higginſon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Hodgkins,</hi> Church<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>warden of Stepny, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Pert,</hi> Knight, and Sir Peter Garenſers Knight, anciently of Normandy, and one of the longlind Proge<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nitors of the learned Doct. Theophilus Garenſers, of Clarken-well, M.D. from which family he is lineally deſcended.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Charles Gerbier,</hi> ſon of Sir Balthazar Gerbier.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edvardus Blomley,</hi> Armig. heir of that ancient family of the Blomleys in Cheſheir, whence Laurence Blomely of the Inner Temple Eſq; and Counſellor at Law, of a good ſtanding, is original deſcended.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Avis Gybſon,</hi> and afterwards dame Avis Knevet, builder af the Free-ſchool of Rat<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cliffe, where the ingenious Mr Speed Maſter of Arts, is the incumbent Maſter.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Morley,</hi> and Ralph Morley, ſons of the late Sir Thomas Morley Knight, one of the Longlind Ance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtors, of theſe two long Knightly &amp; ancient Families of the Morleys in Suſſex.</item>
               <pb n="46" facs="tcp:45532:28"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ralph Leventhorp,</hi> of Albu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ry-Hall, <hi>comit. Hartf.</hi> Eſq; one of the Anceſtors to the noble Sir Tho. Leventhorp, <hi>com. praed.</hi> Knight and Bar. ronet, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Theodore Mayerne,</hi> Knight, Phyſitian to the late King.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Am. Poulet,</hi> Knight ſome<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>times Governor of Jerſey.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Lumley,</hi> eldeſt ſon of the right honourable the Lord Viſc. Richard Lumley of Stanſtead.</item>
               <item>Captain <hi>Barrow,</hi> the fourth ſon of Col. Barrow of Dul<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lin.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Anthony Berkley,</hi> Eſq;, of the noble family of the Bercleys of Berckly Caſtle, <hi>com.</hi> Glo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ceſt. of which the truly right honourable the Lord George Barckley, is the longlind Progenitor.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Charles Mercer,</hi> ſon of Sir John Mercer, Knight.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Reynolds,</hi> Eſq; Clark of his Majeſties Privy Seal.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Corvet,</hi> of Sprow<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſton, <hi>com. norf.</hi> Baronet.</item>
               <item>Dame <hi>Margaret,</hi> Counteſs of Richmond, Mother of Hen<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ry the ſeventh.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Tho. Ruſſel,</hi> Eſq; ſon an heir of Sir William Ruſſel of Strenſham, in the County of Worceſt. Knight Bar.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mathew Crutchfield,</hi> of an an<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cient family of that name, in the <hi>com.</hi> of Oxford, a worthy Citizen and Draper of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Alan Broderick,</hi> ſon of Sir Thomas Broderick Knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Henry Saintjohns,</hi> Knight, and Garter king at Arms, a branch of that moſt ancient, and long knighly family of the Saint johns of Lyddiard, in the County of Wilts, of which Sir Walter Saintjohns Baronet, <hi>ſtilo veteri,</hi> is the chief.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ambroſs Randolph,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Medlicoat,</hi> Eſq; father of Thomas Medlycoat of the middle Temple, Eſq; and Counſellor at Law; and alſo of his brother Mr Edmond Medlycoat, an Officer of and in the Court.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Merrick,</hi> wife of Sir William Merrick Knight, L.L.D. and Judge of the high Court of Admiralty.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth Philipps,</hi> daughter of the late Sir Henry Prat,
<pb n="47" facs="tcp:45532:28"/> Baronet, and ſiſter of the now Sir George Prat of Col<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſil Baronet, and wife of Francis Philipps, Eſq; one of the ſeniores and readers of the illuſtrious ſociety of the Inner Temple, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Howel,</hi> late Hiſtoria<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>grapher to his preſent Ma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>jeſty.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Peter Lemair,</hi> Knight, a memorable Benefector.</item>
               <item>Mr <hi>Skearn,</hi> of Yorkſhire, a good Benefactor.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Charles Sanford,</hi> ſon of John Sandford, Eſq; one of the Heraulds at Arms, now li<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ving.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Sherrington,</hi> of Sherrington-hall, and Cran<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>worth, Knight; of the ſelf ſame line of that truly noble family of the Sherringtons in Lancaſhire, from whence that highly heroick Collonel <hi>William Sherrington,</hi> an e<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>minent and ſuccesful Com<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mander, in the Venetian ſer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vice; and alſo his very near and worthy Kinſman Willi-Sherrington the Turkie Mer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chant (with others of that renowned race) are origi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nally deſcended.</item>
               <item>Coll. <hi>William <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>nderwood,</hi> fa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther of George Underwood, of Kenſington, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Nelſon,</hi> ſon of Mr John Nelſon, Gent. and Mer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chant of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Suſanna Lydcot,</hi> wife of Col<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lonel Leonard Lydcot, and daughter of Sir John Len<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thal Knight, and Marſhal of the Kings Bench.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Reynolds,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Alexander Purpoint.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Palmer,</hi> Batchelor of Divinity.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Blanch Perry,</hi> chief Gentle<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>woman to Q. Elizabeths pri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vy chamber.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Tomkins,</hi> ſecond ſon of James Tomkins of Moning<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ton, in the C. of Hereford, Eſq;</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Alexander Tomkins,</hi> the fifth ſon of Richard Tomkins of Monington, Eſq; both of them the very near Allies of the now Sir Thomas Tom<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>kins of Monington, Knight, a member of Parliament, and ever an active ſervant to, and paſſive ſufferer for their Majeſties.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Francis Edgeoak,</hi> of Edge<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>oak C. Worſt. Knight.</item>
               <pb n="48" facs="tcp:45532:29"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mary Edgerion,</hi> only daugh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ter of Sir Thomas Edgerton, Knight Baronet, baron of Elſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mere, and Lord high Chan<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cellor of England, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Birkhead,</hi> Eſq; bro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther to Major Birkhead of Holborn, Citizen and Gold<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſmith of London.</item>
               <item>Lady <hi>Dorothy Stafford,</hi> wife and widdow to Sir William Stafford, Knight, daughter to Henry Lord Stafford, the only ſon and heir of Edward the laſt Duke of Bucking<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ham, of that moſt noble and princly name.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Alexander Davis,</hi> of Ebury, in the C. of Middleſex, Eſq; brother to Sir Thomas Da<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vis, Knight and Sheriff of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edmund Hammond,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ann Loker,</hi> daughter of Wil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>liam Loker of Oaking, in the County of Surry, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Arundel,</hi> of Guarnick, <hi>com corn.</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Laurence,</hi> Merchant.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Margaret Chute,</hi> daughter of Sir George Chute of Stock-wel, Knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chriſtopher Wood,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Hannah Barrow,</hi> daughter of Mr Giles Barrow, Wollen<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>draper.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Beſtone,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Brigham,</hi> Eſq; Con<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>trouler to George and Wil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>liam, Arch-biſhops of Can<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>terbury.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Bancraft,</hi> biſhop firſt of London, and next Arch<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>biſhop of Canterbury.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Scot,</hi> Eſq; deſcended from the ancient barons of Bawery in Scotland.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Thirleby,</hi> biſhop of Ely.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Charles Maſon,</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Robert Harlow,</hi> Eſq; a branch of that ancient and knightly family of the Harlows in Hereford-ſhire, from whence Sir Edward Harlow Knight of the bath, and Colonel Sir Rober Harlow his bro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther, are lineally deſcended.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Henry Skipwith,</hi> Eſq; ſon of Sir Richard Skipwith, Kt. deſcended from the Skip<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>withs in Yorkſhire, from Hugh, ſon of Baldrick, one of the ancienteſt barons of the Realm.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>George Paul,</hi> Knight.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ann Roberts,</hi> wife of Ralph Roberts of Briſtol, a memo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rable
<pb n="49" facs="tcp:45532:29" rendition="simple:additions"/> Citizen, &amp;c.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Bayles,</hi> of the middle Temple Eſq; very ancient<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ly of Potters Newton, in the County of York Eſquires; one of the Pregenitors of John Bayles of Wilby, in the County of Suffolk, Eſq; now living; and of his bro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther Thomas Bayles one of the benchers of the middle Temple Eſq; and Counſel<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lor at Law; who with his young ſon and heir Oneale Bayles, (there alſo admit<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ted) compleateth ſeven de<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fcents of that name &amp; family which have-been members of that Illuſtrious ſociety.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Lucy Evans,</hi> wife of George Evans of the County of Gloceſt. anciently Gentle<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man, and daughter of Mrs Framces Forsbrook, wife of the late Richard Forsbrook, anciently of the County of Northampton, Eſquires and Gentlemen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Cremer,</hi> Eſq; and Alderman of London, anci<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ently of Leton in Norfolk; from whence the now Sir John Cremer of Sechee, in the ſame County, knight, and late High Sheriff thereof together with his Nephew Charles Cremer of Snetiſham, Eſq; and Counſellor at Law, in the Illuſtrious ſociety of Grays Inn, are originally deſcended.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Adam Poultney,</hi> a moſt me<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>morable Patriot, the builder of that fair Church of S. Laurence Poultney, born of a worthy family of that name of Miſterton in Lei<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ceſterſhire; from which long<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lin'd and knightly family for many generations, Sir Wil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>liam Poultney of S. James, knight and Juſtice of Peace, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> is originally and un<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>interruptedly deſcended, with others elſewhere men<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tioned.</item>
               <item>Doct. <hi>William Drury,</hi> Judge of the Prerogative Court; a branch of that ancient and once flouriſhing family of the Druries in Norfolk, and elſewhere.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Busby,</hi> a memorable Patriot, one of the ance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtors of Sir John Busby of Buckinghamſhire, and of the moſt eminently learned and exemplarily obliging Do<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ctor
<pb n="50" facs="tcp:45532:30"/> Richard Busby, Preben<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dary of Weſtminſter, and many years the moſt happy Maſter of that ſo famous Freeſchool.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Dudley Palmer,</hi> of Grays Inn Eſq; ſon and heir of Sir Anthony Palmer, knight of the bath.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>George Humble,</hi> Eſq; father of Sir William Humble of Stratford-Langton, <hi>com. Eſſ.</hi> Knight and Baronet, now living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ann Dryden,</hi> wife of John Dryden, of the County of Northampton, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Dry field,</hi> Knight, Lord Maior of London.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>William Talmage,</hi> (or Ta<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lamach) knight, one of the longlin'd Anceſtors of Sir Lionel Talmage, of the County of Suffolk.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Courtney,</hi> knight, ſon of the then Earl of De<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vonſhire; which Earls of Devonſhire, were the noble Progenitors of that Illuſtri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ous &amp; Princely Familyof the Courtneys, time out of mind, in that County; from whom the now living Sir William Courtney is lineally deſcended.</item>
               <item>Lord <hi>John Vere,</hi> Earl of Ox<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ford.</item>
               <item>Lord <hi>Awbery Vere,</hi> ſon and heir of the ſaid John Earl of Oxford, and both of them (with many other Peers of that name) the high-born Progenitors of the Right Honourable and truly he<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>roick Lord Awbery Vere, the Earl of Oxford now li<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ving.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas</hi> Lord <hi>Rutherford,</hi> Ba<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ron of Hunthil, and Husband of the right honourable Bridget Baroneſs Ruther<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ford, and daughter of Sir Alexander Urquhart knight, and one of the ancienteſt families in the kingdom of Scotland.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Job Harby,</hi> knight, father of the late Sir Job Harby knight, and both Grand-fa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther, and Father of Sir E<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>raſmus Harby of Hartford<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſhire, now living.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Cook,</hi> knight of the Bath, Lord Maior of London, 1462. deſcended from a good Family of that name in Norfolk, and one of the Anceſtors of that worthy family of the Cooks of Hind<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ham-Hall
<pb n="51" facs="tcp:45532:30"/> near Gloceſter, from whence William Cook Eſq; and Lieutenant-Colonel in that County, and Colonel Edward Cook his brother (both ſon of the late Sir Robert Cook, and Nephews of the living Colonel Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas Cook) are lineally de<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſcended.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>Thomas Wroth,</hi> of Pether<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ly Park <hi>Com.</hi> Summerſ. of the ſame Family of thoſe Wroths of Durance, in the County of Middleſex, and Sir John Wroth, whoſe name and Family appeareth by the Authentique teſtimony of old dateleſs Records, to be one of the ancienteſt in that County; of which ſeat of Durance, Sir Henry Wroth now living, is the in<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>combent Proprietor.</item>
               <item>Sir <hi>John Scoriſditch,</hi> a me<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>morable, and exceeding ancient knight, ſometimes the Proprietor of Scoriſdich, corruptly called, and vul<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>garly ſuppoſed Shoares<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ditch, from Jane Shoare there dying; the which Sir John Scoriſditch (among other goodly Mannors) was the Proprietor of Ickenham, in the County of Middleſex, which is ſtill in the hands of Scoriſditch Eſq; now there living.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Matthew Parker,</hi> Arch-biſhop of Canterbury.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Margret Parker,</hi> wife of the ſaid Matthew.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Cristopher Wormeal,</hi> of Lam<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>beth, Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Turner,</hi> there alſo interred.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth Friend,</hi> wife of Roger Friend.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Frances Frome,</hi> wife of Mr John Frome, Citizen.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth Colledge,</hi> wife of Ralph Colledge.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Agnes Tydnam,</hi> wife firſt of Thomas Marſhal, next of John Manning.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Bayliffe,</hi> and <hi>Elizabeth</hi> his wife.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth Baſſock.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth Taverner.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Southes,</hi> Gent.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>William Juxton,</hi> Biſhop firſt of London, Lord Treaſurer of England, Arch-biſhop of Canterbury, and Uncle to Sir William Juxton, ancient<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ly of Suſſex; and the Re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>verend and eminently learn<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ed
<pb n="52" facs="tcp:45532:31"/> D. Robert Poary, Reſi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dentiary Prebend of S. Pauls, <hi>&amp;c.</hi> who beſtowed the ſaid Arch-biſhops Atchievement, as an Ornament to Lambeth Church.</item>
               <item>The Lord <hi>Caroone,</hi> Embaſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſador Leidger from the States of Holland, his At<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chievement in the ſame Church.</item>
               <item>Doctor <hi>Daniel Featly,</hi> a moſt memorable Divine.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Tredeſcant,</hi> the famous Collector and Conſerver of antiquities.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Maſon,</hi> eldeſt ſon of Richard Maſon, Yeoman of the Guard.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Katharine Moore,</hi> daughter of William and Margaret Moore, of Reading.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Fredericus a Becker,</hi> a Gentle<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man of Holland.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mary Tediman,</hi> wife of Chri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtopher Tediman: ſhe was eldeſt daughter of Sir Tho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas Tediman knight, <hi>&amp;c.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Peter Hills,</hi> one of the Aſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſiſtants in the Trinity-houſe.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Rodger Tweedy,</hi> Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomaſin Paſefield,</hi> wife of George Paſefield, Eſq;.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Brian, Richard, Mary, Alice,</hi> and <hi>Elizabeth,</hi> two ſons and three daughters of Richard Reynolds, Citizen and Goldſmith of London.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Richard Hubbart,</hi> Inhabitant of Redriff.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Mary Packston,</hi> daughter of Rodger Packſton.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Wats,</hi> Inhabitant of Re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>driff.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Jane Pepper,</hi> widdow of Ni<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cholas Pepper, and daugh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ter of Captain Henry Tedi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>man.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>James Hocket,</hi> Marriner, Ma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſter of the Trinity-houſe.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Marret.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Barter.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John, William,</hi> and <hi>Eliza<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>beth Price.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elizabeth Whaley,</hi> wife of Ro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ger Whaley of London, Salter.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ellen Hedgecock,</hi> wife of Ro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bert Hedgecock.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Elle York,</hi> daughter of Ed<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mond York.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Headly,</hi> Marriner.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>John Croncar.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edmond Hudſon.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Milleſcent Willis,</hi> wife of Ro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bert Willis.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Thomas Garret.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Edward Patience,</hi> and <hi>Grace Gibſon</hi>
               </item>
            </list>
            <pb facs="tcp:45532:31"/>
         </div>
      </body>
   </text>
</TEI>
